[{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-01","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Electrocuted"]},{"preventability":["Low","Medium","High"]},{"howPreventable":["Bypass circuit"]},{"incidentLocation":["Attic space"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60010.015 - Employee Is ElectrocutedAccident: 60010.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 04/01/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966067.015 04/02/2014 Power Electric Services, Inc.At approximately 3:00 p.m. on April 1, 2014, Employee #1, an electrician, bypass ed the circuit to the exterior lighting because the system was on a timer and heneeded to assess the lighting to determine why one of the three canned lights w as inoperative. He determined that the ballast must have been out on the one light. He entered an attic space and began to work on the lighting system. Employee #1 was later found electrocuted.Keywords: ballast--lighting, electric arc, electrocutedEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966067.015 27 M Fatality Electricians","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":1,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-12","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-03-12"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Heart Attack"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Call 911"]},{"incidentLocation":["Wal-Mart Stores East I, L.P."]},{"missingEquipment":["None"]},{"missingPrograms":["None"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60029.015 - Employee Suffers A Heart AttackAccident: 60029.015 -- Report ID: 0112300 -- Event Date: 03/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name965811.015 04/03/2014 Wal-Mart Stores East I, L.P.At 10:00 p.m. on March 12, 2014, an employee clocked out of work at the end of h is shift. The employee got into his car, attempted to depart work, returned to aparking spot, exited his vehicle, approached a co-worker outside the store and asked him to call 911. The employee sufferred a fatal heart attack and died.Keywords: heart attackEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 965811.015 72 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":2,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-03","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-04-03"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["accidental discharge"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["fi lling it with air"]},{"incidentLocation":["Stuttgart"]},{"missingEquipment":["multipiece rim wheel"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60049.015 - Employee Is Killed By Exploding TireAccident: 60049.015 -- Report ID: 0627100 -- Event Date: 04/03/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966252.015 04/03/2014 Stuttgart Blue Seal Petroleum, Inc.At 10:00 a.m. on April 3, 2014, an employee was leaning over a back hoe tire, fi lling it with air, when the tire exploded. The employee sustained head injuries andwas killed.Keywords: accidental discharge, air pressure, amputation, backhoe, multipiece rim wheel, struck by, tireEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966252.015 65 M Fatality Automobile mechanic apprentices","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":3,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60050.015 - Employee Is Struck By A Customer Vehicle And KilledAccident: 60050.015 -- Report ID: 0625700 -- Event Date: 03/31/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966234.015 04/03/2014 The Home Depot Usa, Inc.At 11:08 a.m. on March 31, 2014, an employee was walking in the parking lot, nea r a handicap parking area. A driver of a Toyota Tundra, 4-door pick-up truck rolled past a STOP bar on the wrong side of the isle and struck the employee. The f ront driver's side tire was on top of the employee's left leg. The driver backed upthe truck to get off of the employee. The employee was taken to hospital whe re he later died. He sustained fractures to the head and left leg.Keywords: head, leg, motor vehicle, struck by, truckEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966234.015 68 M Fatality Janitors and cleaners","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":4,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-02","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["electrocuted"]},{"preventability":["high"]},{"howPreventable":["PPE, appropriate safety equipment, employee training and safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["utility pole"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE and/or appropriate safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training and safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60051.015 - Employee Is Electrocuted By Contact With Power LineAccident: 60051.015 -- Report ID: 0626300 -- Event Date: 04/02/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966246.015 04/02/2014 East Texas Utility Services Inc.At approximately 9:30 a.m. on April 2, 2014, Employee #1 and three coworkers wer e replacing an existing single-phase conductor with a three-phase conductor ona utility pole. Employee # 1 was working from the elevated bucket of a truck-mou nted aerial device on the east side of a utility pole. The east side of the poleconsisted of live overhead line, 14,400 volts. The west side of the pole consis ted of the new dead overhead lines being installed. Employee #1 came into contac twith the live lines and was electrocuted.Keywords: aerial lift, boom, electrical, electrocuted, struck againstEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966246.015 51 M Fatality Electrical power installers and repairers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":5,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-03","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Falling Object","Struck-By"]},{"preventability":["High"]},{"howPreventable":["Ensure that all employees are wearing the proper safety equipment and using machines and tools appropriate for the nature of the job. Use safety nets or platforms to ensure that falling objects can be contained."]},{"incidentLocation":["Gulf Island, LLC"]},{"missingEquipment":["Hard hat","eye protection","face shield","gloves","protective clothing"]},{"missingPrograms":["Training on use of protective clothing and equipment","safe cutting practices"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60069.015 - Employee Is Crushed And Killed By Falling Steel PlateAccident: 60069.015 -- Report ID: 0625700 -- Event Date: 04/03/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966312.015 04/04/2014 Gulf Island, LlcAt 8:45 p.m. on April 3, 2014, Employee #1 was welding a pad eye underneath a st eel plate as a coworker cut the tacks that were holding it to an I-beam. Employee #1 was struck and crushed by the falling 4,455 lb steel plate and was killed.Keywords: beam, crushing, falling object, steel plate, struck by, weldingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966312.015 41 M Fatality Structural metal workers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":6,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-04","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Chemical burn"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Missing Equipment such as PPE, Missing Programs such as employee training or safety awareness"]},{"incidentLocation":["Haverhill Chemicals Llc"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60129.015 - Employee Is Killed From Chemical Burns While Clearing A BlocAccident: 60129.015 -- Report ID: 0522000 -- Event Date: 04/04/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966352.015 04/05/2014 Haverhill Chemicals LlcAt 10:30 p.m. on April 4, 214, an employee and a coworker were attempting to cle ar a gravity fed drain line from a reactor. The coworker was stationed on the second level of the facility watching for liquid movement while the employee was o n the first level of the facility adding steam to the drain line. The two worker were inradio contact and were approximately 100 to 120 feet away from each oth er. The employee reported a leak at the ethylene expansion joint. The employee w assprayed with phenol, hydrochloric acid, acetone, and bisphenol A. The coworke r heard the accident over the radio and was the first to respond. Emergency personnel were summoned to the facility and the employee was transported to a hospit al by ambulance. Employee received chemical burns and was killed.Keywords: accidental discharge, chemical, chemical burn, hydrochloric acid, reactorEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966352.015 61 M Fatality Chemical technicians","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":7,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60149.015 - Employee Is Burned And Killed While Performing Maintenance OAccident: 60149.015 -- Report ID: 0627510 -- Event Date: 04/04/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966461.015 04/05/2014 S & S Equipment & Supply, Inc.At 1:30 p.m. on April 4, 2014, an employee finished changing a valve assembly an d sight glass on the bottom port of the sight glass on a 4 by 20 heater treaterthen climbed the heater treater to an approximate height of 7 feet to replace th e valve assembly and sight glass on the top port of the sight glass. The employe eremoved the upper valve assembly from the heater treater to replace it, allowi ng oil, gas, and water to spew from the open port in the heater treater. The emp loyeewas sprayed with a mixture containing oil, water, and gas. The vapors from the mixture quickly ignited causing fatal burns. The employee was wearing fire retardantclothing and was extinguished within minutes with water. The employee was burned and died.Keywords: burn, fire, lockout/tagout, maintenance, protective clothingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 966461.015 28 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":8,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-02","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fall"]},{"preventability":["High"]},{"howPreventable":["Failure to use appropriate"]},{"incidentLocation":["Exterior masonry"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60169.015 - Employee Falls From Scaffold And Is KilledAccident: 60169.015 -- Report ID: 0215000 -- Event Date: 04/02/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966558.015 04/02/2014 Pak National Gen. Corp.At approximately 12:00 a.m. on April 2, 2014, Employee #1 fell approximately fou r stories off a tubular welded scaffold and was killed.Keywords: fall, scaffoldAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther building Alteration or rehabilitation $50,000 to $250,000 14 150 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 966558.015 58 M Fatality Construction laborers FallDist: 80FallHt:80Cause: Exterior masonryFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":9,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-04","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fatality"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Unknown"]},{"incidentLocation":["commercial grill conveyor"]},{"missingEquipment":["uncooked poultry"]},{"missingPrograms":["food preparation"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60170.015 - Employee Dies SuddenlyAccident: 60170.015 -- Report ID: 0215600 -- Event Date: 04/04/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966556.015 04/07/2014 Gourmet BoutiqueAt 5:00 p.m. on April 4, 2014, an employee was placing uncooked poultry onto a c ommercial grill conveyor when the employee died from unknown causes.Keywords: food preparationEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 966556.015 27 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":10,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60249.015 - Employee Is Crushed And Killed By Falling Well EquipmentAccident: 60249.015 -- Report ID: 0522500 -- Event Date: 04/05/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966767.015 04/07/2014 Lee SpecialtiesAt 3:30 p.m. on April 5, 2014, an employee was standing on the top cap of a step ladder while disconnecting oil and gas well equipment using a mobile crane's hoisting device. The equipment was being removed from the well head in preparation for the well's first hydraulic fracturing operation. The equipment weighed approximately 10,595 lbs. Two coworkers were holding the base of the step ladder whi le the employee was disconnecting the well equipment. The equipment tippedaway from the employee who stepped backwards and fell approximately 8 ft. One coworke r fell in a different direction. The other coworker ran clear of the fallingequ ipment. The equipment tipped back towards the employee, became disconnected from the crane's hoisting device, and fell on the employee. The employeewas crushed and killed. The coworkers were unharmed.Keywords: amputation, blowout--oil well, crane, crushing, fall, falling object, hoist, ladder, material handling, oil well drilling/servicing, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966767.015 43 M Fatality Supervisors, production occupations","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":11,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-01","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["gunshot"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["L & W Restaurant Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60269.015 - Employee Is Shot And Killed During RobberyAccident: 60269.015 -- Report ID: 0213400 -- Event Date: 04/01/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966802.015 04/07/2014 L & W Restaurant Inc.At 8:30 p.m. on April 1, 2014, an employee was delivering a take-out food order to a residence. The employee was robbed, shot, and murdered as he wasdelivering the take-out food order.Keywords: gunshot, workplace violenceEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 966802.015 50 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":12,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60310.015 - Employee Is Crushed And Killed By A Falling CounterweightAccident: 60310.015 -- Report ID: 0524500 -- Event Date: 04/10/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967170.015 04/10/2014 K & M Equipment, Inc.At 12:00 p.m. on April 10, 2014, an employee completed sandblasting two counterw eights and requested the forklift driver stand the next counterweight on end. The counterweight was 3 ft by 4 ft by 3 in. The employee was working alone. The em ployee did not come to the break area for lunch and following lunch the supervisor went to the yard to check. The supervisor found the employee unresponsive lay ing on the ground with a counterweight laying on his lower chest and abdomen.Th e employee was struck by the counterweight and sustained traumatic asphyxia. The employee was killed.Keywords: asphyxiated, crushed, maintenance, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 967170.015 52 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":13,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-01","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-04-01"]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Email":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":["Galmor's / G&G Steam Services, Inc."]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["run over & crushing"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["using brakes or proper parking of the dozer"]},{"incidentLocation":["on an uphill slope"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60311.015 - Employee Is Run Over By Dozer And Is KilledAccident: 60311.015 -- Report ID: 0627700 -- Event Date: 04/01/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967168.015 04/02/2014 Galmor'S / G&G Steam Services, Inc.At 2:00 p.m. on April 1, 2014, an employee was dismounting a dozer parked on an uphill slope, the dozer began moving down slope The dozer ran over, crushed,and killed the operator.Keywords: brake, construction vehicle, crushing, run overAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther heavy construction New project or new addition $50,000 to $250,000 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 967168.015 33 M Fatality Equipment Operator: Heavy FallDist:FallHt:Cause: ExcavationFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":14,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60312.015 - Employee Is Killed When Saw Kicks BackAccident: 60312.015 -- Report ID: 0830500 -- Event Date: 04/08/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966757.015 04/08/2014 Gopher Excavation, Inc.At approximately 3:15 p.m. on April 8, 2014, Employee #1 was using a hand held g asoline Stihl cut-off saw, Model TS700, to cut 8-in. high-density polyethylene municipal water line. Employee #1 removed the manufacturer\u0000s abrasive blade and i nstalled a 14-in. carbide tipped saw blade prohibited by the manufacturer in theoperators manual and warning stickers placed on the saw. The saw kicked back st riking Employee #1 in the throat and chest area. Employee #1 was killed.Keywords: kick back, neck, saw, struck byAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityPipeline Maintenance or repair $50,000 to $250,000 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 966757.015 30 M Fatality Excavating and loading machine operators FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Trenching, installing pipeFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":15,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60329.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By A Rotating Stock On A LatheAccident: 60329.015 -- Report ID: 0317900 -- Event Date: 04/08/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name966624.015 04/08/2014 Roll Former CorporationAt 10:00 a.m. on April 8, 2014, an employee was polishing a roller shaft on a Vi ctor Model 1640 lathe at 1800 rpm. The tail stock of the roller shaft was not lo ckedin, and the rotation caused the shaft to bend, which struck the employee's chest causing blunt force trauma and he was killed.Keywords: chest, lathe, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 966624.015 61 M Fatality Machinists","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":16,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-09","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Employee is struck and killed by a front-end loader"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Inspect area before walking through it"]},{"incidentLocation":["Union Pumping, L.P."]},{"missingEquipment":["Safety equipment like helmets of protective clothing."]},{"missingPrograms":["Safety awareness programs."]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60349.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By A Front-End LoaderAccident: 60349.015 -- Report ID: 0626000 -- Event Date: 04/09/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967321.015 04/09/2014 Union Pumping, L.P.At approximately 6:15 a.m. on April 9, 2014, Employee #1 was walking through an area where a front end loader was being operated when he was struck andkilled.Keywords: crushed, front end loader, industrial truck, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 967321.015 38 M Fatality Truck drivers, light","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":17,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-11","standardCategories":[{"Product":["truck model 146 750, serial number 101398426, license plate number C613"]},{"Organization":["Peter E. Reid Stevedoring, Inc"]},{"PersonType":["Employee #1","Employee # Inspection"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["run over"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["set the parking brake, use wheel chocks"]},{"incidentLocation":["materials warehouse"]},{"missingEquipment":["rock"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60351.015 - Employee Is Run Over By Truck And Is KilledAccident: 60351.015 -- Report ID: 0936300 -- Event Date: 04/11/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967344.015 04/11/2014 Peter E. Reid Stevedoring, IncAt 11:30 a.m. on April 11, 2014, Employee #1 was backing a yard truck, model 146 750, serial number 101398426, license plate number C613 with an attachedcontain er to the dock of the materials warehouse to be unloaded. Employee #1 left the t ruck with the transmission in neutral, and did not engage the parkingbrake, or place the wheel chocks. Employee #1 walked to the steps of the warehouse and met with the warehouse supervisor to exchange paperwork. A forkliftoperator picked up a pallet and drove into the container. The warehouse supervisor saw the cont ainer move a little and notified the forklift operator. The forkliftoperator co ntinued positioning the pallet in the container and the container moved about a foot away from the dock. The warehouse supervisor screamed to theforklift opera tor to stop. As the truck and container started to roll away, the employee tried to place a rock under a wheel to stop it but the truck continued to rolldown t he slope. Then the employee tried to jump onto the step of the cab as it was rol ling across the highway but fell and was run over by the wheels of the truck.Th e employee was crushed by the truck and killed.Keywords: chock, motor vehicle, run over, struck by, truck, wheelEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 967344.015 49 M Fatality Truck drivers, heavy","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":18,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60369.015 - Employee Sustains Electrical Burns And Is KilledAccident: 60369.015 -- Report ID: 0627510 -- Event Date: 04/10/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967308.015 04/10/2014 Park Tower ApartmentsAt 9:15 a.m. on April 10, 2014, an employee was advancing category five wire com munication wire from a pool area to the ground floor at an apartment complex.In vestigation and security video revealed that the employee entered a transformer closet with no warning signs, training, or personal protective equipment. Transformer electrical buses were in close proximity to the holes that were drilled in the floor and the ceiling to route the wiring. The employee came in contact wit h highvoltage electricity. A witness stated the employee was found lying on the hall way floor with charred clothing and skin from the arc flash created by con tact with thetransformer. The employee died at the hospital.Keywords: asphyxiated, burn, electricalEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 967308.015 43 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":19,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60370.015 - Employee Is Killed In Explosion At Well SiteAccident: 60370.015 -- Report ID: 0317500 -- Event Date: 02/11/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name958206.015 02/11/2014 Cameron International CorporationAt 6:45 a.m. on February 11, 2014, an employee was assisting a coworker with che cking a heater that warms a well head. They were waiting to attend a meeting,b ut had heard a \"hissing\" sound and walked toward the well heads. They found tha t the heater wasn't working. The coworker turned to walk towards the heater unit when an explosion knocked him to the ground. The employee was consumed by the fire and was killed.Keywords: explosion, fire, heater, oil well drilling/servicingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 958206.015 27 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":20,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-12","standardCategories":[{"event":["Accident Report DetailAccident","Two Employees Are Killed When Crane Over TurnsAccident"]},{"organization":["Mass Bay Electrical Corp"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["crane overturned"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["properly use truck crane"]},{"incidentLocation":["at approximately 1:45 p.m. on April 12, 2014"]},{"missingEquipment":["electric line vibration dampeners"]},{"missingPrograms":["safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60389.015 - Two Employees Are Killed When Crane Over TurnsAccident: 60389.015 -- Report ID: 0111400 -- Event Date: 04/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967471.015 04/12/2014 Mass Bay Electrical Corp.At approximately 1:45 p.m. on April 12, 2014, Employee #1 was replacing electric al line vibration dampeners from a personnel platform and Employee #2 wasoperat ing an overloaded truck mounted crane. The crane turned over and fell to the gr ound and Employee #1 and Employee #2 were killed.Keywords: crane, crushed, overturn, truck craneAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityPowerline, transmission line Alteration or rehabilitation $50,000 to $250,000 130 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 967471.015 34 M Fatality Electrical Power-Line FallDist: 130FallHt:160Cause: Installing equipment (HVAC and other)FatCause:2 967471.015 34 M Fatality Electrical and electronic engineers FallDist: 130FallHt:160Cause: Installing equipment (HVAC and other)FatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":21,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-09","standardCategories":[{"Location":["Roof"]},{"Product":["Shingles"]},{"PersonType":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["providing guardrails or a harness"]},{"incidentLocation":["roof"]},{"missingEquipment":["guardrails or a safety harness"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60409.015 - Employee Falls From Roof And Is KilledAccident: 60409.015 -- Report ID: 0830100 -- Event Date: 04/09/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967497.015 04/10/2014 Jared Langley Enterprises Inc.At approximately 8:00 a.m. on April 9, 2014, Employee #1 was removing shingles f rom a roof when he fell 9 feet to the ground and was killed.Keywords: fall, roof, roofer, struck againstAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalitySingle family or duplex dwelling Maintenance or repair Under $50,000 1 9 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 967497.015 51 M Fatality Roofers: Helpers FallDist: 9FallHt:9Cause: RoofingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":22,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-03","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-04-03"]},{"IP":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Email":[]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":["Global Industrial Services, Llc"]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Crushed and killed by falling steel plate"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Ensuring all safety procedures are followed"]},{"incidentLocation":["Global Industrial Services, Llc"]},{"missingEquipment":["Protective gear for employees working with heavy objects"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training and safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No."},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No."}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60429.015 - Employee Is Crushed And Killed By Falling Steel PlateAccident: 60429.015 -- Report ID: 0625700 -- Event Date: 04/03/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967515.015 04/08/2014 Global Industrial Services, LlcAt 8:45 p.m. on April 3, 2014, Employee #1 was welding a pad eye underneath a st eel plate as a coworker cut the tacks that were holding it to an I-beam. Employee #1 was struck and crushed by the falling 4,455 lb steel plate and was killed.Keywords: beam, crushed, falling object, steel plate, struck by, weldingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 967515.015 42 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":23,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-12","standardCategories":[{"Location":["Porter Roofing Contractors, Inc."]},{"Organization":["Porter Roofing Contractors, Inc.","Inc."]},{"PersonType":["Employee #1","Employee","#1"]},{"Product":["wheel barrel"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["improve the strength of the roof"]},{"incidentLocation":["roof"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE, safety lanyard, safety harness"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training, safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60449.015 - Employee Falls From Roof And Is KilledAccident: 60449.015 -- Report ID: 0418200 -- Event Date: 04/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967544.015 04/12/2014 Porter Roofing Contractors, Inc.At approximately 9:30 a.m. on April 12, 2014, Employee #1 was dropping off an em pty wheel barrel and picking up a full one on a roof. He stepped on a weak areaand fell through the roof to the concrete 30 feet below. Employee #1 sustained severe head trauma and died later.Keywords: fall, head, roof, struck againstAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityCommercial building Maintenance or repair $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 1 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 967544.015 20 M Fatality Roofers FallDist: 30FallHt:30Cause: RoofingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":24,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-12","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Organization":["Weatherford International Ltd."]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Collapse"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Employee training on cardiac health"]},{"incidentLocation":["Workplace"]},{"missingEquipment":["None"]},{"missingPrograms":["None"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60469.015 - Employee Collapses And Dies Of Heart AttackAccident: 60469.015 -- Report ID: 0627510 -- Event Date: 04/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967563.015 04/13/2014 Weatherford International Ltd.At 10:00 a.m. on April 12, 2014, an employee collapsed while talking on phone an d died of possible heart attack.Keywords: collapseEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 967563.015 54 M Fatality Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":25,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-14","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Organization":["Dwight Plumbing And Heating, Inc."]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["PPE or safety equipment, employee training or safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["roof"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE or safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60489.015 - Employee Falls From Roof And Is KilledAccident: 60489.015 -- Report ID: 0213100 -- Event Date: 04/14/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967622.015 04/15/2014 Dwight Plumbing And Heating, Inc.At approximately 10:30 a.m. on April 14, 2014, Employee #1 was examining an exha ust vent cover that was rattling on a roof. He fell approximately 80 feet and died.Keywords: fall, roof, struck againstEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 967622.015 39 M Fatality Heating, air conditioning, and refrig. mechanics","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":26,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60550.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By A TractorAccident: 60550.015 -- Report ID: 0627700 -- Event Date: 04/14/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967719.015 04/15/2014 Lamunyon Drilling, L.L.C.At 11:15 a.m. on April 14, 2014, an employee was helping erect mud pits during d errick erection. The employee went to the tool trailer to get bolts to install f loorplate. A tractor being used as a forklift was backing up and turning to the driver's right when the left front tire struck and knocked the employee to the ground. Theemployee was caught under the forks and was dragged approximately 20 ft. The employee sustained a fractured skull and was killed.Keywords: derrick, dragged, head, struck by, tractorEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 967719.015 24 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":27,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-16","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["PPE, safety equipment, employee training, safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["4th floor balcony"]},{"missingEquipment":["ladder"]},{"missingPrograms":["safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60589.015 - Employee Falls From Balcony And Is KilledAccident: 60589.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 04/16/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name968174.015 04/16/2014 Jonathon Custom BuildersAt approximately 11:00 a.m. on April 16, 2014, Employee #1 was on a 4 foot step ladder on the 4th floor balcony installing a membrane to the exterior. He fell o ff aladder four stories and received a broken arm. He was hospitalized and die d during surgery.Keywords: arm, fall, fracture, ladder, roofAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt Fatality4 42 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 968174.015 43 M Fatality Carpenters FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Exterior carpentryFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":28,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-17","standardCategories":[{"Location":["Graham Lumber Company, Llc"]},{"Person":["Employee","#1","Employee #1"]},{"Product":["Pitchfork"]},{"Event":["Accident","Sustain A Head Injury And Is Killed","Killed"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Head Injury"]},{"preventability":["High"]},{"howPreventable":["Use Protective Equipment e.g. Safety Helmet"]},{"incidentLocation":["Graham Lumber Company, Llc"]},{"missingEquipment":["Protective Equipment e.g. Safety Helmet"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee Training/Safety Awareness Programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60629.015 - Employee Sustains A Head Injury And Is KilledAccident: 60629.015 -- Report ID: 0419400 -- Event Date: 04/17/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name968371.015 04/18/2014 Graham Lumber Company, LlcAt 8:15 p.m. on April 17, 2014, an employee was using a pitch fork to scrap mate rial on a bark belt waste conveyer and sustained a possible head injury and waskilled.Keywords: conveyor, headEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 968371.015 21 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":29,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-17","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-04-17"]},{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Wear fall protection"]},{"incidentLocation":["roof"]},{"missingEquipment":["fall protection"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60669.015 - Employee Falls From Roof And Is KilledAccident: 60669.015 -- Report ID: 0636900 -- Event Date: 04/17/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name968693.015 04/17/2014 Juan GarciaAt approximately 3:00 p.m. on April 17, 2014, Employee #1 was working on a roof and was not wearing any fall protection. Employee #1 fell and was killed.Keywords: fall, fall protection, head, roofAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityMulti-family dwelling Maintenance or repair $50,000 to $250,000 2 20 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 968693.015 29 M Fatality Roofers FallDist:FallHt:Cause: RoofingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":30,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-20","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["heart attack"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["proper safety and health guidelines"]},{"incidentLocation":["residential gas line"]},{"missingEquipment":["proper protective gear"]},{"missingPrograms":["adequate employee training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No."},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No."}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60709.015 - Employee Dies From A Heart AttackAccident: 60709.015 -- Report ID: 0215600 -- Event Date: 03/20/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name965438.015 03/21/2014 Consolidated EdisonAt 7:00 p.m. on March 20, 2014, an employee was digging an excavation to service a potential leak in a residential gas line. He collapsed while working in the h oleand he died from a heart attack.Keywords: heart attackEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 965438.015 44 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":31,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-17","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Address":[]},{"IP":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Email":[]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":["Banes Roofing, Inc."]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall","head","lost balance"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["insufficient visibility due to spotlights being used on the roof"]},{"incidentLocation":["roof"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60729.015 - Employee Falls From Wall And Is KilledAccident: 60729.015 -- Report ID: 0317900 -- Event Date: 04/17/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name969430.015 04/18/2014 Banes Roofing, Inc.At approximately 2:00 p.m. on April 17, 2014, Employee #1 was using an electric hammer drill to fasten edging to a brick wall. The extension cord was stuck so hestood up and pulled the cord which released and he lost his balance and fell over the wall. Employee #1 received a fracture skull and died.Keywords: fall, head, lost balance, roof, struck againstAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityCommercial building Maintenance or repair $50,000 to $250,000 3 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 969430.015 41 M Fatality Roofers FallDist:FallHt:Cause: RoofingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":32,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-13","standardCategories":[{"Aaddress":[]},{"IP":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Email":[]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":[]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Burn","Explosion","Fire"]},{"preventability":["Low","Medium","High"]},{"howPreventable":["Upgrade electrical system","Insert a bus plug into an energized switch gear"]},{"incidentLocation":["Electrical room"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE","Safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training","Safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"Was this a positive user expierence?":"No"},{"Did this help to solve the problem?":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60769.015 - One Employee Killed, One Injured In Electrical FireAccident: 60769.015 -- Report ID: 0626300 -- Event Date: 04/13/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name970850.015 04/17/2014 Electric, Inc.At approximately 7:13 a.m. on April 13, 2014, Employee #1 was upgrading an elect rical system in an electrical room. Employee #2 was working in a nearby room.E mployee #1 inserted a bus plug into an energized switch gear, 480-volt, when an explosion and fire occurred. Employee #1 was burned and later died from hisinju ries at a hospital. Employee #2 received second degree burns while putting out the fire.Keywords: burn, electrician, explosion, fireAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther building New project or new addition $50,000 to $250,000 2 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 970850.015 64 M Fatality Electrical and electronic engineers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":33,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-15","standardCategories":[{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Email":[]},{"IP":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":["Accident Report DetailAccident","Fall Into Digester Tank And Is Killed","On April 15, 2014","Employee Falls Into Digester Tank And Is Killed","At 12:00 p.m. on April 15, 2014","The employee stepped back and fell into a floor hole and fell30 feet into a digester tank.","The employee sustained fractures and chemical and thermal burns and was killed.","chemical, confined space, fall, floor opening, fracture, guard, heat, pressure vessel, tank, toxic atmosphere"]},{"Organization":["S & S Sprinkler Company Llc"]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":["employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["accident","fall"]},{"preventability":["low","medium","high"]},{"howPreventable":["installing plumbing, lighting fixtures"]},{"incidentLocation":["digester tank"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60789.015 - Employee Falls Into Digester Tank And Is KilledAccident: 60789.015 -- Report ID: 0418600 -- Event Date: 04/15/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name972610.015 04/16/2014 S & S Sprinkler Company LlcAt 12:00 p.m. on April 15, 2014, an employee was carrying the bottom of a 28 foo t extension ladder. The employee stepped back and fell into a floor hole and fe ll30 feet into a digester tank. The employee sustained fractures and chemical a nd thermal burns and was killed.Keywords: chemical, confined space, fall, floor opening, fracture, guard, heat, pressure vessel, tank, toxic atmosphereAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther heavy construction New project or new addition Under $50,000 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 972610.015 33 M Fatality Pipelayer FallDist: 40FallHt:40Cause: Installing plumbing, lighting fixturesFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":34,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-23","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Heart Attack"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Enforcing safety regulations"]},{"incidentLocation":["Paterson Pickle Company"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training and safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60809.015 - Employee Sustains Heart Attack While Operating Fork Lift AndAccident: 60809.015 -- Report ID: 0214500 -- Event Date: 04/23/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name973796.015 04/23/2014 Paterson Pickle CompanyAt 5:30 a.m. on April 23, 2014, an employee was loading pallets onto a truck usi ng a fork lift when the employee sustained an apparent heart attack and died.Keywords: heart attack, powered industrial vehicleEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 973796.015 65 M Fatality Industrial truck and tractor equipment operators","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":35,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-17","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["heart attack"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["employee training or safety awareness programs that could have prevented this incident"]},{"incidentLocation":["Stencel & Son Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE or safety equipment that could have prevented this incident"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs that could have prevented this incident"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60810.015 - Employee Dies Of A Heart AttackAccident: 60810.015 -- Report ID: 0213400 -- Event Date: 04/17/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name973797.015 04/23/2014 Stencel & Son Inc.At approximately 1:45 p.m. on April 17, 2014, Employee #1 returned from lunch an d collapsed and died of a possible heart attack.Keywords: heart, heart attackEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 973797.015 55 M Fatality Carpenters","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":36,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60829.015 - Employee Struck And Killed By A Falling Work BasketAccident: 60829.015 -- Report ID: 0625400 -- Event Date: 04/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name973801.015 04/14/2014 Integrity Services, LlcAt 6:45 p.m. on April 12, 2014, two employees were working from a material baske t that had been placed on a forklift. The basket was elevated approximately 7 feet and the basket was not secured to the forklift. The basket began to fall off the forks and Employee #1 jumped clear and Employee #2 fell out and was struck b ythe material inside the basket on the back and the chest. Employee #2 was kill ed.Keywords: crushing, falling object, oil well drilling/servicing, unsecured, unstable loadEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 973801.015 29 M Fatality Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":37,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60830.015 - Employee Crushed By Lawn Mower Is KilledAccident: 60830.015 -- Report ID: 0316100 -- Event Date: 04/22/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name973863.015 04/23/2014 U.S. Army Garrison, ApgAt 9:15 a.m. on April 22, 2014, an employee was assigned to cut the grass. The employee was riding a Toro Zero Turn Mower around Gate 24. There was a slopedar ea which was being mowed at the time. The Toro Zero Turn Riding Mower turned ove r onto the employee and he was crushed and killed.Keywords: crushing, roll-overEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 973863.015 61 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":38,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-20","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Caught between","Struck by"]},{"preventability":["Low","Medium","High"]},{"howPreventable":["Connect the snub line"]},{"incidentLocation":["Sidewinder Drilling Inc"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60831.015 - Employee Is Caught Between Top Drive And Pull Line Of TongsAccident: 60831.015 -- Report ID: 0627510 -- Event Date: 04/20/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name973859.015 04/21/2014 Sidewinder Drilling Inc.At 9:15 p.m. on April 20, 2014, Employee #1 was part of a crew that was installi ng a casing tool. The employee was holding the tongs in position to tighten thecasing running tool while the snub line was not connected. Employee #1 was stru ck-by and caught between the top drive and the pull line of the tongs and was killed.Keywords: caught between, struck by, tongsEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 973859.015 31 M Fatality Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":39,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-17","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-04-17"]},{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Organization":["Madrid Drywall, Llc"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["PPE or safety equipment"]},{"incidentLocation":["commercial building"]},{"missingEquipment":["rowing","scaffold"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60832.015 - Employee Falls From Scaffold And Is KilledAccident: 60832.015 -- Report ID: 0626300 -- Event Date: 04/17/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name973868.015 04/23/2014 Madrid Drywall, LlcAt approximately 4:00 p.m. on April 17, 2014, Employee #1 was working from a one -tier mobile scaffold installing interior ceiling tiles. He fell from the scaff old,struck his head, and died.Keywords: fall, head, scaffoldAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityCommercial building New project or new addition $250,000 to $500,000 1 10 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 973868.015 63 M Fatality Drywall installers FallDist: 6FallHt:6Cause: Installing interior walls, ceilings, doorsFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":40,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-16","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["let go of the hand truck"]},{"incidentLocation":["south Walton County, Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["hand truck"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60849.015 - Employee Falls From Truck And Is KilledAccident: 60849.015 -- Report ID: 0419700 -- Event Date: 03/16/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name964338.015 03/17/2014 Caring And Sharing Of South Walton County, Inc.At 9:00 a.m. on March 16, 2014, an employee was rolling a TV cabinet using a two -handed hand truck to off-load it The employee continued off the truck, not letting go of the hand truck. The employee fell and broke his second and third verte brae, and was killed.Keywords: fall, vertebraEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 964338.015 76 M Fatality Managers and administrators, n.e.c","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":41,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-14","standardCategories":[{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":[]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["fall protection"]},{"incidentLocation":["Oil Rig"]},{"missingEquipment":["fall protection"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60869.015 - Employee Falls Off Oil Rig And Is KilledAccident: 60869.015 -- Report ID: 0625700 -- Event Date: 03/14/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974080.015 03/17/2014 Scrap Cutting, Inc.At 1:00 p.m. on March 14, 2014, an employee went up to the high part of an old d rilling rig to cut a beam. The beam swung and the employee tried to outrun it. The beam hit the employee, knocking him into a hole on the rig floor and onto PVC pipes, before landing on the ground. The employee fell approximately 60 to 70feet and later died. The employee was not wearing fall protection.Keywords: elevated work platform, fall, fall protection, rigging, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974080.015 30 M Fatality Misc. metal,plastic,stone&glass-working mach. op's","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":42,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-22","standardCategories":[{"Email":[]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":[]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[{"Employee #1":["974142.015","26M","Fatality","Construction Laborers"]}]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["drown","fall","floor opening"]},{"preventability":[]},{"howPreventable":[]},{"incidentLocation":[]},{"missingEquipment":[]},{"missingPrograms":[]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60889.015 - Employee Falls Through Hatch Into Tank And DrownsAccident: 60889.015 -- Report ID: 0626000 -- Event Date: 04/22/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974142.015 04/22/2014 Infinity Maintenance Services, L.P.At approximately 11:45 a.m. on April 22, 2014, Employee #1 was pulling up a 3-in ch fire hose from ground level to the walking working platform he was standing on, approximately 32 feet. He fell through an open man way hatch to the bottom o f a tank and drowned.Keywords: drown, fall, floor openingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974142.015 26 M Fatality Construction laborers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":43,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-24","standardCategories":[{"Address":[]},{"DateTime":["2014-04-24"]},{"Email":[]},{"Event":[]},{"IP":[]},{"Location":[]},{"Organization":["General Construction Company"]},{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"PersonType":[]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"URL":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Caught in","Crushing","Drill","Drowning","Flowing material","Pile driver","Trench"]},{"preventability":[]},{"howPreventable":[]},{"incidentLocation":[]},{"missingEquipment":[]},{"missingPrograms":[]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60989.015 - Employee Falls Into Trench And DrownsAccident: 60989.015 -- Report ID: 0522000 -- Event Date: 04/24/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974469.015 04/25/2014 Complete General Construction CompanyAt approximately 11:45 a.m. on April 24, 2014, Employee #1 and coworkers were co nstructing a footing system for a new two lane bridge. An 8 foot wide by 20foot long by 12 foot deep trench had been dug and protected with eight 4 foot stacke d trench boxes. Three shafts were to be bored in the bottom of the trench thatw ould extend approximately 35 foot to the ground. The footing on the west side of the creek sat right on the existing shore line of the creek so a pad was constructed out into the creek for the drill rig and other equipment to sit on and wor k from. Coworkers were pumping water out of the trench box. Employee #1 was working the pumps and went over to the drill rig which was sitting on the pad to ass ist the drill rig operator to remove a 54 inch auger bit and place the muck buck et onto clean the shafts out. Employee #1 was standing on the pad when the grou nd collapsed and he went down into the collapsing ground. Rescue squads were called quickly but Employee #1 could not be rescued due to the unstable condition of the new hole filled with soil, rock, water and debris. Employee #1 was swallowed in the hole where he stayed for approximately 10 hours, pinned by rocks and dirt and drowned.Keywords: caught in, crushing, drill, drowning, flowing material, pile driver, trenchAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityBridge New project or new addition $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 974469.015 44 M Fatality Laborers, except construction FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Pile drivingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":44,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 60990.015 - Two Employees Are Killed, Two Injured From Dust ExplosionAccident: 60990.015 -- Report ID: 0626600 -- Event Date: 04/26/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974475.015 04/27/2014 Georgia-Pacific LlcAt 6:30 p.m. on April 26, 2014, employees were responding to a fire within the s anding dust collection system. The employees were standing next to a dust collector when an explosion occurred and the vents on the bag house blew off which exp osed the employees to fire. The employees sustained burns to multiple bodyparts and were killed.Keywords: burn, combustible dust, explosion, fire, protective clothingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974475.015 58 M Fatality Electricians2 974475.015 63 M Hospitalized injury Electricians3 974475.015 58 M Hospitalized injury Electricians4 974475.015 56 M Fatality Electricians","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":45,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-21","standardCategories":[{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Location":[]},{"Organization":["Crown Roofing Llc"]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Address":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Email":[]},{"DateTime":[]},{"IP":[]},{"Person":[]},{"PersonType":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Drowning","Fall","Fracture","Head"]},{"preventability":[]},{"howPreventable":[]},{"incidentLocation":["Residential construction"]},{"missingEquipment":[]},{"missingPrograms":[]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61009.015 - Employee Falls From Roof And Is KilledAccident: 61009.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 04/21/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name970750.015 04/21/2014 Crown Roofing LlcAt approximately 12:15 p.m. on April 21, 2014, Employee #1 was installing a tile roof of a 6:12 pitch roof, approximately 10.8 foot high. He was applying a ceme ntbase mixture to the cap tiles. Later in the day coworkers found Employee #1 i n the deep end of the partially filled pool. Employee #1 died from injuries to h is headfrom a fall and drowned.Keywords: drowning, fall, fracture, head, residential construction, roofAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalitySingle family or duplex dwelling New project or new addition $250,000 to $500,000 1 11 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 970750.015 33 M Fatality Roofers FallDist: 11FallHt:11Cause: RoofingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":46,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-28","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["falling object"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["Milan Manufacture, Inc"]},{"missingEquipment":["Personal protective equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61031.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By Falling Wood PlanksAccident: 61031.015 -- Report ID: 0418800 -- Event Date: 04/28/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974695.015 04/28/2014 Milan Manufacture, Inc.At 1:45 p.m. on April 28, 2014, an employee was removing wood planks while stand ing on a stack of wood. The employee fell. The employee was struck by thefallin g wood planks. Various wood planks fell on top, covering the employee. The emplo yee was killed.Keywords: falling object, planking, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974695.015 49 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":47,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-28","standardCategories":[{"Organization":["Science Applications International Corp"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["drowning"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["personal floatation device (PFD) or air supply system"]},{"incidentLocation":["San Diego Bay"," NAS North Island north boat launch","Seaplane Ramp #10"]},{"missingEquipment":["personal floatation device (PFD)","Air Supply System","SCUBA","Rebreather"]},{"missingPrograms":["Safety Observer"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"no"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"no"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61049.015 - Employee Drowns While Swimming With Sea LionsAccident: 61049.015 -- Report ID: 0936200 -- Event Date: 04/28/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974744.015 04/29/2014 Science Applications International Corp.At 9:00 p.m. on April 28, 2014, a sea lion training crew was conducting training exercises in San Diego Bay near the NAS North Island north boat launch, also called Seaplane Ramp #10. The ramp was approximately 50 feet wide. Prior to the in cident, the employee was dropped off at the beach and swam from the beachinto t he water near the west wing of the ramp. Two sea lions successfully located him south of the pier's west wing. The employee was to move to the north side ofthe west wing but a third sea lion failed to find him there. After a search by the employee's co-workers, he was spotted underwater under the ramp. CPR andadvance d life support was administered but were unsuccessful. The employee wore a wetsu it and a 17 pound weight belt but did not have a personal floatationdevice (PFD ) or air supply system such as SCUBA or rebreather. He was in the water by hims elf at night with no designated safety observer and the employeedrowned.Keywords: access/egress, caught in, drowningEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 974744.015 29 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":48,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-28","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-04-28"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Struck and Killed by Motor Vehicle"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Safety Equipment, Employee Training, Safety Awareness Programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["Highway, Road, Street"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee Training, Safety Awareness Programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61069.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By Motor VehicleAccident: 61069.015 -- Report ID: 0627700 -- Event Date: 04/28/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974724.015 04/28/2014 Traffic & Lighting Systems, LlcAt approximately 9:45 a.m. on April 28, 2014, Employee #1 was working at a pedes trian signal light. A vehicle left the road and became airborne and struck Employee #1 and killed him.Keywords: crushed, flagger, motor vehicle, struck byAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityHighway, road, street Alteration or rehabilitation $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 0 0 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Construction1 974724.015 48 M Fatality FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Installing equipment (HVAC and other)FatCause:2 974724.015 46 M Fatality FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Installing equipment (HVAC and other)FatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":49,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61090.015 - Employee Falls, Hits Head And Dies LaterAccident: 61090.015 -- Report ID: 0626700 -- Event Date: 03/28/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974839.015 04/28/2014 Plant Process EquipmentAt 9:00 a.m. on March 28, 2014, an employee was walking towards the electrical s hop. The employee tripped on a wooden pallet that was put in place to act as a step leading to the entrance of the electrical shop. As a result of the fall, t he employee fractured his wrist and hit his head on metal grating. He was taken to aConcentra Clinic for evaluation that same day. On March 31, 2014, the emplo yee called in sick and did not report to work, on April 1, 2014, the employee's sonfound him dead on the floor of his home. Preliminary autopsy report states c ause of death was a result of complications from work related accident. The empl oyerwas made aware of the autopsy information on April 25, 2014, and subsequent ly reported the fatality on April 28, 2014.Keywords: elevated work platform, fall, fracture, head, wristEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974839.015 61 M Fatality Management related occupations, n.e.c.","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":50,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61091.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By Falling PipeAccident: 61091.015 -- Report ID: 0626600 -- Event Date: 04/29/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974850.015 04/30/2014 Womble Company, Inc.At approximately 2:55 p.m. on April 29, 2014, Employee #1 was attempting to stra ighten pipe on the second layer of a rack that was crooked. As the pipe was being straightened, it shifted, falling off of the back of the rack. Employee #1 wa s flung into the air and landed on the ground near-by. Employee #1 suffered inj uriesto his face and head and a dislocated shoulder. Employee #1 died form the injuries.Keywords: dislocated, face, fall, head, shoulder, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 974850.015 35 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":51,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-25","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Organization":["Bison Drilling & Field Services Llc"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["crushed"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["drivers training","equipment maintenance"]},{"incidentLocation":["derrick"]},{"missingEquipment":["safety harnesses"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61109.015 - Employee Is Crushed Between A Man Lift And A Monkey Board AnAccident: 61109.015 -- Report ID: 0627500 -- Event Date: 04/25/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974882.015 04/26/2014 Bison Drilling & Field Services LlcAt 7:15 p.m. on April 25, 2014, a coworker was removing a monkey board from a de rrick by removing a pin. The monkey board shifted and fell on an employee thatw as leaning on the man lift. The employee was crushed and killed.Keywords: crushed, derrick, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974882.015 56 M Hospitalized injury Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":52,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-07","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Employee Falls From Ladder And Is Killed"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Reduce Height of Ladder"]},{"incidentLocation":["Home Depot U.S.A., Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["Protective Head Gear"]},{"missingPrograms":["Safety Training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61110.015 - Employee Falls From Ladder And Is KilledAccident: 61110.015 -- Report ID: 0418800 -- Event Date: 03/07/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974884.015 04/30/2014 Home Depot U.S.A., Inc.At 6:30 p.m. on March 7, 2014, an employee was standing on a nine-rung step ladd er rearranging shelves. The employee suddenly fell from the ladder onto thegrou nd. According to the Medical Examiner's investigation the employee received a bl unt impact head trauma in the fall.Keywords: fall, head, ladderEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974884.015 67 M Fatality Sales workers, hardware and building supplies","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":53,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61129.015 - Employee Is Crushed Under A Dock Ramp And KilledAccident: 61129.015 -- Report ID: 0522000 -- Event Date: 04/30/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974926.015 04/30/2014 SpartannashAt 1:00 a.m. on April 29, 2014, a truck driver arrived at a warehouse with a ful l trailer. The employee then was to drive an empty trailer back to the originati nglocation. The employee was instructed to sweep up the trailer, which was loca ted on the south east side at dock #45, remove items or equipment inside the tra iler,and place them inside the perishable side of the warehouse. The employee o pened the warehouse rolling door of dock # 45 and stepped into the pit to open t hetrailer door. The dock leveler, also called the \u0000ramp,\u0000 was a Kelly model HV6 15. This style of ramp is stored in a vertical position unlike traditional ramps stored in ahorizontal position. The victim stepped out of the pit to lower the ramp onto the trailer by pulling a chain. Once the chain is pulled the hydrauli cs are activated andreleased and lower the ramp onto the trailer. The ramp did not lower due to the support leg holding it in the vertical position. The employ ee stepped inside the pitwhich was approximately 6 ft by 8 ft by 10 ft and rais ed the support leg. The ramp lowered onto the employee'\u0000s chest. The employee wa s found unresponsive bya coworker approximately one hour later. The employee su stained compressional asphyxia and was killed.Keywords: asphyxiated, caught in, crushing, falling object, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974926.015 65 M Fatality Truck drivers, heavy","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":54,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-25","standardCategories":[{"Person":["employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["power washing skid loaders"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["PPE"]},{"incidentLocation":["Turner County Dairy"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61149.015 - Employee Is Caught By Boom Of Skid Loader And KilledAccident: 61149.015 -- Report ID: 0830300 -- Event Date: 04/25/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974968.015 04/28/2014 Turner County DairyAt 11:30 a.m. on April 25, 2014, an employee was power washing skid loaders. The employee reached to release levers outside of the cab. The boom lowered,pullin g the employee down. The employee sustained cuts around abdomen and chest and wa s killed.Keywords: agriculture machinery/vehicle, boom, caught in, skidderEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974968.015 21 M Fatality Farm equipment mechanics","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":55,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-14","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall","ladder","ladder jack scaffold"],"preventability":["low","medium","high"],"howPreventable":["correct usage of safety equipment and training"],"incidentLocation":["Gary D. Casper"],"missingEquipment":["PPE"],"missingPrograms":["safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61189.015 - Employee Falls From Ladder And Is KilledAccident: 61189.015 -- Report ID: 0317500 -- Event Date: 04/14/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974991.015 05/05/2014 Gary D. CasperAt approximately 3:45 p.m. on April 14, 2014, Employee #1 fell, 5.5 feet, either from a ladder or ladder jack scaffold. He received broken ribs and a collapsed lungand died.Keywords: fall, ladder, ladder jack scaffold, lung, rib, scaffoldEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974991.015 60 M Fatality Carpenters","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":56,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61209.015 - Employee Is Struck By Falling Steel Beam And KilledAccident: 61209.015 -- Report ID: 1032500 -- Event Date: 04/30/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975230.015 04/30/2014 Rule Steel Tanks, Inc.At 10:30 a.m. on April 30, 2014, an employee was standing close to the end of a 50 ft. steel beam while a Gradall forklift operator attempted to roll the steel beamon the forks of a Caterpillar to reposition the beam for installation. The beam rolled off of the forks, onto the ground, and struck the employee's chest. The employeewas killed.Keywords: falling object, material handling, powered industrial vehicle, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 975230.015 53 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":57,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-02","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-02"]},{"IP":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Email":[]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":["M And W Logistics"]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":["Employee"]},{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fatality"]},{"preventability":["Medium"]},{"howPreventable":["Barricade area of construction zone"]},{"incidentLocation":["Highway, road, street"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61289.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By Motor VehicleAccident: 61289.015 -- Report ID: 0418300 -- Event Date: 05/02/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975413.015 05/02/2014 M And W LogisticsAt 3:30 a.m. on May 2, 2014, an employee was testing the compaction of the pavem ent. A car entered the barricaded area of the construction zone and struck thee mployee. The employee was killed due to being struck by the motor vehicle.Keywords: motor vehicle, struck byAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityHighway, road, street Alteration or rehabilitation $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 975413.015 59 M Fatality Engineering technicians, n.e.c. FallDist:FallHt:Cause: PavingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":58,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61309.015 - Employee Falls From Roof And Is KilledAccident: 61309.015 -- Report ID: 0215000 -- Event Date: 04/14/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967535.015 04/14/2014 Bas Renovation Corp./First Astoria Construction Co. Inc. Joint VentureAt approximately 3:45 p.m. on April 14, 2014, Employee #1 was working on a roof with no fall protection. He was attempting to come down from the roof to the ledge when he fell approximately 110 feet and was killed.Keywords: fall, fall protection, roofAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityCommercial building Maintenance or repair $500,000 to $1,000,000 12 110 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Construction1 967535.015 35 M Fatality FallDist: 110FallHt:110Cause: Exterior claddingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":59,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-21","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fatality"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["n/a"]},{"incidentLocation":["F.G. Gamez, Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["n/a"]},{"missingPrograms":["n/a"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61310.015 - Employee Is Found Dead Lying Beside A Plastic Bin In A FruitAccident: 61310.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 04/21/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974474.015 04/23/2014 F.G. Gamez, Inc.At 4:30 p.m. on April 21, 2014, an employee was working in a grove collecting fr uit harvest. The employee was found lying on the ground by a coworker. No substances and or objects were found nearby. The employee was found dead.Keywords: agricultureEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974474.015 51 M Fatality Farm workers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":60,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61311.015 - Employee Falls Through Skylight And Is KilledAccident: 61311.015 -- Report ID: 0626000 -- Event Date: 04/21/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975087.015 04/29/2014 Isla RestorationAt approximately 11:30 a.m. on April 21, 2014, Employee #1 was painting the exte rior wall of a structure located next to and above a skylights on a ceiling in t heatrium area on the 4th floor. The ceiling was made of six, 4 foot by 4 foot s kylights. He was using a Genie, articulating, 60-64 foot boom aerial lift. He was using afull body harness and a lanyard attached to the anchor point located inside the aerial lift basket. He aligned the aerial basket above the ceiling and disconnected hislanyard from his full body harness. He exited the aerial l ift basket and fell 11.25 feet through one of the skylights, striking his head o n the concrete floor. Employee#1 sustained a traumatic head injury and died a few days later at the hospital.Keywords: aerial lift, fall, fall protection, head, skylight, struck againstAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityMulti-family dwelling Maintenance or repair Under $50,000 4 11 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 975087.015 37 M Fatality Painters, construction and maintenance FallDist: 11FallHt:11Cause: Exterior paintingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":61,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61312.015 - Employee Falls From Zip Line And Is KilledAccident: 61312.015 -- Report ID: 0936300 -- Event Date: 05/01/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975466.015 05/01/2014 Baldwin Brothers, LlcAt 9:00 a.m. on May 01, 2014, an employee was receiving a guest at the end of # 2 Zip line. This was the employee's third day at work. The employee had receivedsome training on fall protection and zipline procedures and she had been traine d that fall protection was optional on this platform. There was one lanyard avai lableto her. She was wearing a harness, but was not attached to a lanyard. The employee tried to attach the lanyard to the zipline rider as the rider landed on theplatform. The momentum of the rider caused the employee to move toward the edge of the platform and she was pulled off the platform and suspended over a ravine. The employee finally released her grip and fell to the ground, 125 feet be low. The employee was killed as a result of major trauma to the head and body af terlanding on the rock bed of a river in about a foot of water.Keywords: amusement park/carnival, fallEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975466.015 29 F Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":62,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61313.015 - Employee Falls From Flatbed Trailer And DiesAccident: 61313.015 -- Report ID: 0626000 -- Event Date: 03/13/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name970270.015 04/21/2014 Guardian Building Products Distribution, Inc.At 2:30 p.m. on March 13, 2014, an employee was walking on top of a flatbed trai ler towards the back. The employee was seen to stumble backwards and fell offof the flatbed trailer onto concrete at a height of 4 feet and 7 inches. The emplo yee struck his head on the concrete and was killed.Keywords: fall, head, lost balance, tractor trailerEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 970270.015 68 M Fatality Driver-sales workers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":63,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-08","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["drowning"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["Arkansas side of the Mississippi River"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61330.015 - Employee Drowns From Sinking BargeAccident: 61330.015 -- Report ID: 0627100 -- Event Date: 04/08/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967443.015 04/09/2014 Kinder MorganAt 3:315 p.m. on April 8, 2014, an employee was identifying coils located within the barge when the mishap occurred. A loud noise was heard by dock workers andthen the barge suddenly listed towards the Arkansas side of the Mississippi Rive r according to eyewitnesses. When this happened, the barge took on water andsan k within 10 to 15 seconds. The employee drowned in the water.Keywords: drowning, longshoring, shipEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 967443.015 36 M Fatality Laborers, except construction2 967443.015 37 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":64,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-04","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-04"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Diver Almost Drownes"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["safety equipment"]},{"incidentLocation":["60 feet of water"]},{"missingEquipment":["mask"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61350.015 - Diver Almost Drowns, Dies Later From InjuriesAccident: 61350.015 -- Report ID: 1032300 -- Event Date: 05/04/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975043.015 04/30/2014 Furthur Diving Co.At 5:30 p.m. on April 29, 2014, a diver employee was harvesting Geoduck clams in approximately 60 feet of water. The employee came to the surface and said hisu mbilical was tangled and was going back down to untangle it. A few minutes later the employee was seen on the surface without his mask signaling for help, thendisappeared under the water. A second diver located him and brought him to the s urface, he was pulled aboard the Dawn Breaker and transported to EMS, waitingon shore. On May 4, 2014, the employee diedKeywords: diving, drownEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975043.015 24 M Fatality Diver","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":65,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-01","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Struck by Car"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Safety equipment and employee training/safety awareness programs could have prevented this incident."]},{"incidentLocation":["Well Site"]},{"missingEquipment":["Safety Equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee Training/Safety Awareness Programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61351.015 - Employee Is Struck By Car And KilledAccident: 61351.015 -- Report ID: 0627700 -- Event Date: 03/01/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975422.015 04/28/2014 Sampson Brothers Inc.At 11:45 a.m. on March 1, 2014, an employee was changing a natural gas meter cha rt at the well site when he was struck by a 1995 Ford F-150. The employeewas pi nned against the gas meter and house and he was killed.Keywords: natural gas, pin, struck by, truckEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975422.015 72 M Fatality Meter readers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":66,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-05","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["crane","crushed","manhole"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["inadequate protection of employees"]},{"incidentLocation":["trenching","installing pipe"]},{"missingEquipment":["employee"]},{"missingPrograms":["chain attached to the manhole frame"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No."},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No."}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61352.015 - Employee Crushed By A Manhole Frame Is KilledAccident: 61352.015 -- Report ID: 0317500 -- Event Date: 05/05/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975589.015 05/05/2014 Guyer Brothers IncorporatedAt 2:15 p.m. on May 5, 2014, an employee was installing 8\" sewer lines and a man hole frame. The chain attached to the manhole frame was being released andthe e xcavator was moving. The chain got caught on the riser of the manhole frame and slid off, crushing the employee between the manhole frame and the wall ofthe ex cavation thus killing the employee.Keywords: crane, crushed, manholeEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 975589.015 31 M Fatality Laborers, except construction FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Trenching, installing pipeFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":67,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-05","standardCategories":[{"Location":["Bristol Protective Services"]},{"Organization":["Bristol Protective Services"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Carbon Monoxide Poisoning"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Proper ventilation in the trailer"]},{"incidentLocation":["Bristol Protective Services"]},{"missingEquipment":["ventilation in trailer"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training on safety awareness of carbon monoxide poisoning"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61354.015 - Employee Is Killed From Carbon Monoxide PoisoningAccident: 61354.015 -- Report ID: 0213900 -- Event Date: 05/05/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975606.015 05/05/2014 Bristol Protective ServicesAt 6:45 a.m. on May 5, 2014, an employee was sitting in a trailer charging his p hone. The generator used to charge his phone was on and emitting CO into the trailer causing CO poisoning. The employee was killed from Pulmonary Edema.Keywords: carbon monoxide, toxic atmosphereEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 975606.015 29 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":68,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61369.015 - Two Employees Are Struck By Metal From Exploding Sand SeparaAccident: 61369.015 -- Report ID: 0627510 -- Event Date: 04/30/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975580.015 04/30/2014 Ameriflow Energy Services, LlcAt 12:00 a.m. on April 30, 2014, flow-back employees opened the 4H well head tha t was connected to a sand separator which was under pressure. The sandseparator is connected to a sand box collector on one end and a manifold on the other end . Employee #1 was seen closing the valve between the sand separatorand the sand box collector. The pathway from the sand separator and the manifold were closed , including all 5 valves. Employee #2 delivered some product andwalked towards employee #1 to get a haul delivery ticket signed. Both employees were in the pre ssurized zone area of wellhead #4H when the explosionoccurred. The pressure inc reased in the sand separator which was not equipped with a pressure relief valve . According to witnesses, Employee #1 and Employee#1 sustained severe head trau ma from shrapnel released by the exploded metal pressure vessel and were killed.Keywords: air pressure, blowout--oil well, compressed gas, explosion, oil well drilling/servicing, pressure piping, pressure vessel, rigging, struck by, structuralcollapseEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975580.015 40 M Fatality Truck drivers, heavy2 975580.015 46 M Fatality Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":69,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2013-09-10","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall","fracture","hip","slip","tractor trailer"]},{"preventability":["low","medium","high"]},{"howPreventable":["PPE","safety equipment","employee training","safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["Panther Valley Lumber Co."]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE","safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61370.015 - Employee Fractures Hip In Fall And Dies From Surgery ComplicAccident: 61370.015 -- Report ID: 0317700 -- Event Date: 09/10/2013Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967613.015 04/15/2014 Panther Valley Lumber Co.At 8:30 a.m. on September 10, 2013, an employee was helping to unload foam insul ation from a tractor trailer. The employee slipped and fell from the rear of th etrailer to the gravel parking lot, fracturing his left hip. The employee died from complications during surgery to repair his fractured hip.Keywords: fall, fracture, hip, slip, tractor trailerEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 967613.015 54 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":70,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-03","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["crushed","roll-over"]},{"preventability":["low","medium","high"]},{"howPreventable":["employee training or safety awareness programs","PPE or safety equipment"]},{"incidentLocation":["hayfield"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61389.015 - Employee Is Crushed By Atv In HayfieldAccident: 61389.015 -- Report ID: 1032500 -- Event Date: 05/03/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975703.015 05/06/2014 Eagle View Farms, Llc.At 6:00 p.m. on May 3, 2014, an employee was riding a 4-wheel Honda ATV while ch anging irrigation lines in a hayfield. The employee attempted to drive on the side of a slope next to the field and the ATV rolled on top of him. The employee w as crushed and killed by the ATV when it rolled over him.Keywords: atv, agriculture, crushed, roll-overEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975703.015 51 M Fatality Agricultural and food scientists","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":71,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-02","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-02"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["struck by"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["installing better crossing points"]},{"incidentLocation":["residential street"]},{"missingEquipment":["protective gear"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61410.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By VehicleAccident: 61410.015 -- Report ID: 0636900 -- Event Date: 05/02/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975800.015 05/02/2014 F & S ConcreteAt 7:45 a.m. on May 2, 2014, an employee was digging up dirt and loading a wheel barrow. Employee crossed a residential street and was struck by a privatelyown ed vehicle. The employee was killed.Keywords: struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975800.015 57 M Fatality Construction laborers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":72,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61429.015 - Two Employees Are Struck By Metal From Exploding Sand SeparaAccident: 61429.015 -- Report ID: 0627510 -- Event Date: 04/30/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975833.015 04/30/2014 Maverick Coating Services, LlcAt 12:00 a.m. on April 30, 2014, flow-back employees opened the 4H well head tha t was connected to a sand separator which was under pressure. The sandseparator is connected to a sand box collector on one end and a manifold on the other end . Employee #1 was seen closing the valve between the sand separatorand the sand box collector. The pathway from the sand separator and the manifold were closed , including all 5 valves. Employee #2 delivered some product andwalked towards employee #1 to get a haul delivery ticket signed. Both employees were in the pre ssurized zone area of wellhead #4H when the explosionoccurred. The pressure inc reased in the sand separator which was not equipped with a pressure relief valve . According to witnesses, employee #1 and employee#1 sustained severe head trau ma from shrapnel released by the exploded metal pressure vessel and were killed.Keywords: air pressure, blowout--oil well, compressed gas, explosion, flowing material, kick back, oil well drilling/servicing, pressure piping, pressure vessel,rigging, struck by, structural collapseEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975833.015 40 M Fatality Truck Driver: Heavy/Tractor-Trailer2 975833.015 46 M Fatality Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":73,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-06","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Employee falling off the back of a golf cart and striking their head"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Provide proper training and safety equipment such as helmets"]},{"incidentLocation":["Craftsmen On-Site Services, Llc"]},{"missingEquipment":["Helmets"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training, safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve theproblem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61449.015 - Employee Fell Off The Back Of A Golf Car, Struck Head And IsAccident: 61449.015 -- Report ID: 0729700 -- Event Date: 05/06/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975897.015 05/06/2014 Craftsmen On-Site Services, LlcAt 7:30 a.m. on May 6, 2014, a shipping employee was driving an E-Z-GO Fleet Gol f Car and stopped to pick up a passenger and Employee #1, for the purpose ofpro viding them a ride to their shop. Employee #1 was riding / standing on the back of a golf car and fell hitting his head on the pavement, causing him serious head injuries. Employee #1 was transported to a Medical Center where he was pronoun ced dead at 8:45 AM.Keywords: fall, golf cart, head, riding on equipment, struck againstEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975897.015 21 M Fatality Mechanical controls and valve repairers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":74,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-29","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["crane","crushing","elevator","hoist","longshoring","machine guarding","material handling","powered industrial vehicle","ship","shipyard","struck by","suspended load"]},{"preventability":["low","medium","high"]},{"howPreventable":[]},{"incidentLocation":[]},{"missingEquipment":[]},{"missingPrograms":[]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No."},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No."}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61469.015 - Employee Is Crushed Under An Elevator And KilledAccident: 61469.015 -- Report ID: 0213900 -- Event Date: 04/29/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975868.015 04/29/2014 Gloucester Terminals, LlcAt 12:00 p.m. on April 29, 2014, an employee was retrieving items from the space under an elevator within a ship. The elevator lowered on the employee. The employee was caught under the elevator. The employee was crushed and killed.Keywords: crane, crushing, elevator, hoist, longshoring, machine guarding, material handling, powered industrial vehicle, ship, shipyard, struck by, suspended loadEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975868.015 53 M Fatality Longshore equipment operators","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":75,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-06","standardCategories":[{"Organization":["Atlas Roofing Corporation"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fall"]},{"preventability":["High"]},{"howPreventable":["Installing safety equipment and providing training program for employees"]},{"incidentLocation":["Main plant building"]},{"missingEquipment":["Harness, lanyard"]},{"missingPrograms":["Fall protection"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61470.015 - Employee Falls From Roof And Is KilledAccident: 61470.015 -- Report ID: 0627700 -- Event Date: 05/06/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975593.015 05/06/2014 Atlas Roofing CorporationAt 10:50 a.m. on May 6, 2014, an employee was reroofing the main plant building using sheet metal panels. The coworker and supervisors witnessed twoemployees d onning harnesses and securing lanyards. Employee #1 turned to walk towards the catwalk, heard noise, turned and Employee #1 had fallen throughan opening in th e roof, where new sheet metal panels had not yet been placed. Employee #1 was w orking at a height approximately 12 feet above ground level.Per medical examine rs report, Employee #1 was killed from massive head trauma.Keywords: fall, fall protection, head, lanyard, roofAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityManufacturing plant Maintenance or repair 1 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Construction1 975593.015 31 M Fatality FallDist:FallHt:Cause: RoofingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":76,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-08","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Accidental Discharge"]},{"preventability":["High"]},{"howPreventable":["Fire safety protocols and inspections"]},{"incidentLocation":["Infirmary Health System, Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["Protective headgear"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training on fire safety protocols and inspections"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61489.015 - Employee Struck In The Head By A Fire Extinguisher And Is KiAccident: 61489.015 -- Report ID: 0418600 -- Event Date: 05/08/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976003.015 05/08/2014 Infirmary Health System, Inc.At 8:00 a.m. on May 8, 2014, an employee was inspecting fire extinguishers. The fire extinguisher discharged and struck the employee in the head, killing him.Keywords: accidental discharge, compressed gas, fire extinguisher, head, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976003.015 25 M Fatality Fire inspection and fire prevention occupations","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":77,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-07","standardCategories":[{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Email":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":[]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["employee training or safety awareness programs","PPE"]},{"incidentLocation":["heavy construction"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61510.015 - Employee Falls From Aerial Lift And Is KilledAccident: 61510.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 05/07/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976060.015 05/08/2014 Sign Service & Installations, IncAt 3:45 p.m. on May 7, 2014, the employee was inside a basket (just like an aeri al lift basket) assisting in the erection and power driving of a steel column tosupport a two sided billboard, one side was a LED display and on the other a st ationary billboard. Employee fell approximately 60 feet and was killed.Keywords: crane, fall, personnel cage, rigging, struck byAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther heavy construction Alteration or rehabilitation Under $50,000 68 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 976060.015 28 M Fatality Crane and tower operators FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Erecting structural steelFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":78,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-28","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Location":["Black Gold Testing"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["asphyxiation"]},{"preventability":["high"]},{"howPreventable":["safety equipment/PPE","employee training/safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["oil tank"]},{"missingEquipment":["safety equipment/PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training/safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61569.015 - Employee Is Asphyxiated When Gauging An Oil TankAccident: 61569.015 -- Report ID: 0830300 -- Event Date: 04/28/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976233.015 04/28/2014 Black Gold TestingAt 5:00 a.m. on April 28, 2014, an employee was tasked to gauge a crude oil tank . The employee was found face down in the upper hatch of a crude oil storagetan k. The employee was asphyxiated and killed.Keywords: asphyxiated, non-pel overexposure, oil tank, oil well drilling/servicingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976233.015 20 M Fatality Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":79,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-05","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-05"]},{"Product":["natural gas, oil well drilling/servicing"]},{"PersonType":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["cardiac arrest","heart attack"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["providing medical help in time","making sure the employee takes regular breaks","making sure the employee does not work for long hours"]},{"incidentLocation":["4j Well Service, Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["ppe"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No."},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No."}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61570.015 - Employee Dies From Cardiac ArrestAccident: 61570.015 -- Report ID: 0830300 -- Event Date: 05/05/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975798.015 05/08/2014 4j Well Service, Inc.At 4:30 p.m. on May 5, 2014 an employee was operating the controls of a workover rig. The employee began to feel increasingly ill as the workday progressed. Atapproximately 1600 the employee asked for relief from his duty station at the co ntrols of the workover rig because he was feeling too ill to continue work. Theemployee's illness became so great that coworkers felt he was experiencing a hea rt attack and transported him to the hospital. The employee suffered cardiac arrest and died.Keywords: heart attack, natural gas, oil well drilling/servicingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 975798.015 48 M Fatality Drillers, oil well","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":80,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61589.015 - Employee Is Caught In A Dough Mixing Tub And KilledAccident: 61589.015 -- Report ID: 0626700 -- Event Date: 04/27/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974821.015 04/28/2014 Wonton Food CorporationAt 12:00 p.m. on April 27, 2014, an employee was using a pressurized air hose an d wand to release dry flour stuck to the inside of a dough mixing tub. The machine had an opening of 43 3/8 inches by 18 1/4 inches. The opening was 33 inches a bove the floor. The employee placed his upper torso within the point of operations during the mixing tub rotation in an attempt to clean the interior of the tub . The employee was caught between the tub opening and the exterior wall of the machine. The employee was found by a coworker. The employee's upper torso was in the machine and his feet off the ground. The employee sustained severegashes to the head and neck and was killed.Keywords: crushing, food preparation, lockout/tagout, machine guardingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974821.015 26 M Fatality Machine operators, not specified","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":81,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61610.015 - Employee Falls Down Stairs And Is KilledAccident: 61610.015 -- Report ID: 0729300 -- Event Date: 05/07/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976436.015 05/12/2014 Regions BankAt 9:00 p.m. on April 29, 2014, an employee was walking down stairs to the train ing room. The employee fell down several steps to the landing area. The employee complained about pain in her knee and was diagnosed with a broken tibia. She w as treated at the emergency room and released. On May 7, 2014, the employeeretu rned to hospital and died from a pulmonary embolism. The autopsy stated the deat h was a result of the fall.Keywords: embolism, fall, stair, stair landingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976436.015 67 F Fatality Bank tellers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":82,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-02","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-02"]},{"Product":["Komatsu LP Forklift"]},{"Person":["Welder"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Falling Object"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Additional restraints for unstaged materials"]},{"incidentLocation":["Sewer/Water Treatment Plant"]},{"missingEquipment":["Additional Safety Equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee Training & Safety Awareness Programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61629.015 - Employee Struck By Falling Object Is KilledAccident: 61629.015 -- Report ID: 0316700 -- Event Date: 05/02/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name975386.015 05/02/2014 Z-Weldco, Inc.At 11:00 a.m. on May 2, 2015, a welding employee was cutting the middle out of t he baseplate of an elevated hopper bin apparatus. This was done after welding flanges with bolt holes onto the cut legs of another elevated hopper bin apparatu s, so the base could be rejoined with the hopper. The welder was cutting the centerout of the bottom plate of an elevated lime hopper support structure whil e the lime hopper was supported on the forks of a Komatsu LP forklift, SN 135952 . Whenthe center of the baseplate dropped from the lime hopper support structu re the balance of the unsecured and unsupported hopper support structure shifted ; itrotated off of the elevated forks, and fell onto the welder, crushing him u nder the lime hopper bin. The hopper of the unsecured and unsupported elevated l imehopper support structure, containing lime granules, rotated off of the eleva ted forklift forks, and crushed the welder kneeling at its base. The welder sust ainedseveral crush related injuries to the chest, back, abdomen, and extremitie s.Keywords: chemical, crushing, falling object, material handling, powered industrial vehicle, suspended loadAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalitySewer/water treatment plant Alteration or rehabilitation XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 975386.015 30 M Fatality Welders and cutters FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Temporary work (buildings, facilities)FatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":83,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-12","standardCategories":[{"Address":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"DateTime":["2014-05-12"]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Person":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"IP":[]},{"Product":[]},{"URL":[]},{"Location":[]},{"Email":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Falls"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["install proper safety equipment and program training"]},{"incidentLocation":["Concrete floor"]},{"missingEquipment":["scaffold"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee safety practices"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61649.015 - Employee Falls From Scaffold And Is KilledAccident: 61649.015 -- Report ID: 0418100 -- Event Date: 05/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976489.015 05/12/2014 Elite Storage Equipment Erectors, Inc.On May 12, 2014, an employee was using a scissors lift to install wire metal dec king into/onto metal storage racks. The employee was standing on the metal rackwhere he was placing wire metal decking. When the employee was instructed to re turn to the scissor lift, he fell backward approximately 12 feet to the concretefloor below. Employee was killed due to fall.Keywords: fall, scaffoldAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther building New project or new addition Under $50,000 1 12 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 976489.015 41 M Fatality Installers And Repairers FallDist: 12FallHt:12Cause: Installation Of Decking-Final Attachment Deck (WelFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":84,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-11","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-11"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Struck By a Vehicle"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Barricades and Local Police to be positioned ahead of the work zone"]},{"incidentLocation":["Work Zone"]},{"missingEquipment":["Protective Gear"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee Training and Safety Awareness Programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61669.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By A VehicleAccident: 61669.015 -- Report ID: 0627500 -- Event Date: 05/11/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976342.015 05/11/2014 Crane Service Inc.At 2:30 a.m. on May 11, 2014, the employees were attaching the counter weights w hile assembling a CK Kobelco 1600 Crane at the time of the accident. A vehicleb y-passed barricades and local police which were positioned miles ahead of the wo rk zone. Employee #1 was directly hit by the vehicle throwing him into anoutrig ger. Employee #2 was caught-in/between the vehicle and counter weight. Employee #1 was killed and employee #2 suffered an amputation.Keywords: amputation, caught in, crane, motor vehicle, struck byAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityBridge New project or new addition XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 976342.015 39 M Fatality Crane Operator FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Placing bridge girders and beamsFatCause:2 976342.015 54 M Fatality Crane and tower operators FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Placing bridge girders and beamsFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":85,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-11","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fall"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Protected skylight"]},{"incidentLocation":["Roof"]},{"missingEquipment":["Protected skylight"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61670.015 - Employee Falls Through Skylight And Is KilledAccident: 61670.015 -- Report ID: 0317000 -- Event Date: 05/11/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976664.015 05/11/2014 Roman Urethane CorporationAt 4:15 p.m. on May 11, 2014, the employee was working on a roof and fell throug h an unprotected skylight. The employee fell twenty-three (23) feet thus killingthe employee.Keywords: fall, skylightAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityManufacturing plant Maintenance or repair Under $50,000 1 23 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 976664.015 64 M Fatality Painters, construction and maintenance FallDist: 23FallHt:23Cause: Exterior paintingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":86,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-12","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall"]},{"preventability":["medium"]},{"howPreventable":["strict enforcement of safety rules and regulations, proper training and refresher courses, providing of appropriate safety equipment, and the use of appropriate fall protection"]},{"incidentLocation":["Multi-family dwelling"]},{"missingEquipment":["harness","lanyard","safety glasses"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee Training and safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61689.015 - Employee Falls From Mulit-Story Roof And Is KilledAccident: 61689.015 -- Report ID: 0830300 -- Event Date: 05/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976411.015 05/13/2014 Jag Construction LlcAt 12:45 p.m. on May 12, 2014, an employee was installing roof decking during wi ndy conditions on a three-story roof. Employee disconnected his rope grab fromh arness to retrieve a 4' x 8' piece of plywood that flew off the stack from exces sive wind and landed in between roof trusses. As he was carrying it back to thestack, he slipped on a loose piece of plywood and slid and fell off the roof. T he employee was killed due to fall.Keywords: fallAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityMulti-family dwelling New project or new addition $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 3 35 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 976411.015 48 M Fatality Carpenters FallDist: 35FallHt:35Cause: Installation Of Decking-Final Attachment Deck (WelFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":87,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-10","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Location":["Henry J. Varian, Inc."]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fall"]},{"preventability":["High"]},{"howPreventable":["Use of ladder and fully planking scaffold decks"]},{"incidentLocation":["Single family or duplex dwelling"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61710.015 - Employee Falls From Scaffold And Is KilledAccident: 61710.015 -- Report ID: 0111400 -- Event Date: 04/10/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name967436.015 04/11/2014 Henry J. Varian, Inc.At approximately 8:00 a.m. on April 10, 2014, Employee #1 was climbing the insid e frames of a scaffold. The scaffold decks were not fully planked and a ladder was not used to access scaffold levels. Employee #1 attempted to climb over and a round a partially planked deck when he tripped and fell. Employee #1 suffered head and neck injuries and was killed.Keywords: fall, residential construction, scaffold, struck againstAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalitySingle family or duplex dwelling Alteration or rehabilitation $500,000 to $1,000,000 3 40 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 967436.015 72 M Fatality Brickmasons and stonemasons FallDist: 25FallHt:25Cause: Exterior masonryFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":88,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-07","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]},{"Organization":["Farmers Cooperative"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["falls fromtanker truck"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["PPE or safety equipment","employee training or safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["truck"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE or safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61711.015 - Employee Falls From Tanker Truck And Is KilledAccident: 61711.015 -- Report ID: 0728900 -- Event Date: 05/07/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976767.015 05/13/2014 Farmers CooperativeAt 6:00 p.m. on May 7, 2014, an employee was loading fertilizer in a tanker truc k. The employee fell off the truck while loading fertilizer and fractured his sk ull. Theemployee was killed.Keywords: fall, motor vehicleEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976767.015 73 M Fatality Truck drivers, heavy","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":89,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-31","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Killed"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["air pressure, blowout--tire, explosion"]},{"incidentLocation":["Coopersburg Bagging Company"]},{"missingEquipment":["multipiece rim wheel"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61729.015 - Worker Killed When Struck By Wheel/Tire AssemblyAccident: 61729.015 -- Report ID: 0317900 -- Event Date: 03/31/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name974833.015 05/01/2014 Coopersburg Bagging Company, Inc.At 3:30 p.m. on March 31, 2014, an employee repairing tires was struck by an exp loding wheel tire's assembly. The employee suffered head and body blunt forcetr auma and was killed.Keywords: air pressure, blowout--tire, explosion, head, multipiece rim wheel, tireEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 974833.015 60 M Fatality Automobile mechanic apprentices","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":90,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61730.015 - Employee Is Struck By Large Safe And Is KilledAccident: 61730.015 -- Report ID: 0418300 -- Event Date: 05/13/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976812.015 05/16/2014 Daniel TatumAt 5:45 p.m. on May 13, 2014, an employee standing off to the side while a gun safe was being moved up the ramps of the truck. Another coworker (helper #2) stated he was loosing his footing. So another coworker stated to both move out of t he way, so they can let the gun safe fall. As the gun safe was let go, the empl oyeemoved quickly towards the coworker and truck. The gun safe fell on the emp loyee, killing him.Keywords: falling object, gunshot, safeEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976812.015 19 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":91,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61769.015 - Employee Is Struck By Overhead Cargo And Is KilledAccident: 61769.015 -- Report ID: 0626600 -- Event Date: 05/10/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976941.015 05/11/2014 Gulf Stream MarineAt 7:15 p.m. on May 10, 2014, a longshoremen was placing dunnage for cargo to be placed on a vessel. The vessel was loading a 302 metric ton blowoutpreventer (BOP). While the BOP was being lowered, employees started placing dunnage under the skid that was mounted to the bottom of the BOP. This placedthem within inc hes of the skid and directly underneath the BOP, when a pin in the spreader bar came out of its housing causing the wire rope to disengagedropping one side of the BOP to the deck. The skid that was attached to the bottom of BOP became una ttached on one side striking the employee and knockinghim down to the deck. Th e skid then came down landing on the employee's legs causing an amputation of bo th legs. The employee was killed.Keywords: amputation, falling object, hoist, hoisting mechanism, leg, struck by, vessel--containerEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976941.015 61 M Fatality Longshore equipment operators","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":92,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-16","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall","ladder"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["installing a new service into a residential home"]},{"incidentLocation":["Csc Holdings, LLC"]},{"missingEquipment":[]},{"missingPrograms":[]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61770.015 - Employee Falls From Ladder And Is KilledAccident: 61770.015 -- Report ID: 0214700 -- Event Date: 05/16/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976580.015 05/13/2014 Csc Holdings, LlcAt 4:00 a.m. on May 16, 2014, the employee was on a ladder installing a new serv ice into a residential home. The employee fell from the ladder and was killed.Keywords: fall, ladderEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976580.015 26 M Fatality Technicians, n.e.c.","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":93,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61829.015 - Employee Is Killed In A Welding ExplosionAccident: 61829.015 -- Report ID: 0522500 -- Event Date: 05/12/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977120.015 05/13/2014 Sutton Pump & SupplyAt 4:00 p.m. on May 12, 2014, a coworker was welding a lifting eye on the top of a 210 barrel crude oil storage tank. One coworker was tack welding two mild st eelsheets together while the employee was on the top of the 210 tank, welding a lifting eye to the center of the tank. A weld spark or hot slag fell into a th ree inchbung hole that was located on the top of the tank that was approximatel y six inches from the lifting eye, causing the flammable vapors to explode. The explosionmade the tank rise approximately five feet, crushing the employee. Th e employee fell 15 feet to the ground, where he became engulfed in flames. The coworker inthe weld shop was knocked onto his back, receiving minor injuries. The employee that received only minor injuries rushed out of a man door at the b ack of theweld shop and ran around the building to retrieve a fire extinguisher . The employee proceeded to extinguish the employee and then pull the employee out of thehazardous area. Emergency services was called and emergency personne l arrived at the site at 2:38 p.m. The employee was pronounced dead at 4:06 p.m .Keywords: crushing, elevated work platform, explosion, fire, heat, ladder, roof, struck by, weldingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977120.015 29 M Fatality Welders and cutters","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":94,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-16","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-16"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Roll-over"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["proper safety precausions"]},{"incidentLocation":["Construction"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61849.015 - Employee Is Crushed And Killed By Vibratory Compacting RolleAccident: 61849.015 -- Report ID: 0418800 -- Event Date: 05/16/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977171.015 05/16/2014 Cliff'S Trucking Inc.At 9:00 a.m. on May 16, 2014, an employee was driving backwards on a compacting roller. The roller tipped over and the roller fell on top of the employee. Employee was killed from being crushed by the roller.Keywords: construction vehicle, crushing, roll-overAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 3 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 977171.015 54 M Fatality Rolling machine operators FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Backfilling and compactingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":95,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-13","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-13"]},{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["struck by"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["Gibney Tree Expert, Llc"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE or safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61850.015 - Employee Is Struck By Tree Limb And Is KilledAccident: 61850.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 05/13/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977178.015 05/14/2014 Gibney Tree Expert, LlcAt 9:30 a.m. on May 13, 2014, an employee was standing on the ground holding a t agline attached to a tree branch. The branch was cut and it struck employee, killing him.Keywords: struck by, tree, tree felling, tree trimmingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 977178.015 43 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":96,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-23","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["passing out"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["missing equipment or programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["hospital"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61851.015 - Employee Passes Out And Later DiesAccident: 61851.015 -- Report ID: 0418600 -- Event Date: 04/23/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977182.015 05/15/2014 Global Auto Processing Services, LlcAt 4:00 p.m. on April 23, 2014, an employee was blowing out rail cars. The emplo yee complained that he was not able to breath. The employee left work to go to the hospital but passed out and had a car accident. He was taken to the hospital by ambulance. The employee was later released from the hospital, went home andw ent to sleep. He passed away sometime that evening.Keywords: asphyxiated, unconsciousnessEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977182.015 35 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":97,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-04-21","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fall"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Falling protection equipment"]},{"incidentLocation":["Concrete floor"]},{"missingEquipment":["Fall protection"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61889.015 - Employee Falls From Catwalk And Is KilledAccident: 61889.015 -- Report ID: 0729700 -- Event Date: 04/21/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977029.015 05/12/2014 National BeefAt 2:15 a.m. on April 21, 2014, an employee was opening gates on cattle pens. Th e employee was walking on a catwalk and fell off the end of catwalk onto a concrete floor. The employee sustained head injuries and was killed.Keywords: agriculture, catwalk, concrete, fall, fall protection, struck againstEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 977029.015 56 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":98,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-02","standardCategories":[{"Event":["Accident","Inspection Open Date"]},{"Location":["Bryan's Auto East, Ltd."]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Employee Falls From Ladder And Is Killed"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Installation of safety rails around the ladder"]},{"incidentLocation":["Bryan's Auto East, Ltd."]},{"missingEquipment":["Safety equipment such as fall protection gear or hooks on the ladder to prevent slipping."]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training on proper ladder use."]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61909.015 - Employee Falls From Ladder And Is KilledAccident: 61909.015 -- Report ID: 0215600 -- Event Date: 05/02/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name976694.015 05/13/2014 Bryan'S Auto East, Ltd.At 9:15 a.m. on May 2, 2014, an employee was descending a ladder and the ladder slipped, which forced the employee to fall. The employee fractured the L1verteb rae and died later from complications.Keywords: fall, ladderEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 976694.015 65 M Fatality Janitors and cleaners","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":99,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-15","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["collapsed mobile home"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["proper jacking up procedure"]},{"incidentLocation":["southwest corner of the home"]},{"missingEquipment":["safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61929.015 - Employee Is Crushed And Killed From Collapsed Mobile HomeAccident: 61929.015 -- Report ID: 0215800 -- Event Date: 05/15/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977271.015 05/16/2014 Jim Ray Homes, Inc.At 3:38 p.m. on May 15, 2014, an employee was preparing to set a single wide man ufactured home (trailer) onto a gravel base foundation. Employee was workingat the southwest corner of the home were in the middle of jacking the home up. The home shifted and dropped down onto the employee. The employee was killeddue to the collapsed home.Keywords: crushing, falling object, struck byAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalitySingle family or duplex dwelling New project or new addition Under $50,000 1 10 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Construction1 977271.015 60 M Fatality FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Other Activities-Installing Ornamental And ArchiteFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":100,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-14","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Rob Joe Materials Llc"]},{"Location":["Construction Yard"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Employee Is Struck And Killed By Truck"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["By ensuring proper safety protocols are adhered to when operating a construction vehicle"]},{"incidentLocation":["Construction Yard"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE and other safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training and safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61930.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By Truck In Construction YardAccident: 61930.015 -- Report ID: 0636900 -- Event Date: 05/14/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977384.015 05/14/2014 Rob Joe Materials LlcAt 10:00 a.m. on May 14, 2014, the employee had just loaded a backhoe to flat-be d trailer. The employee was behind the truck and was struck by the truck whichkilled the employee.Keywords: construction vehicle, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977384.015 33 M Fatality Heavy equipment mechanics","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":101,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61969.015 - Employee Caught In A Mixing Extruder Is KilledAccident: 61969.015 -- Report ID: 0522000 -- Event Date: 05/20/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977463.015 05/20/2014 Codino'S Limited, Inc.At 1:20 p.m. on May 20, 2014, a 37-year old female employee lifted the mesh guar d on a Lasagna Extruder to check the moisture content of the dough. Theemploye e was trained about a year ago on the operation of the pasta extruder and had ta ken over as the full time operator of the extruder a week prior to the fatalacc ident. The pasta extruder mixes dough that was then used to make lasagna. The ex truder has two rotating shafts at the bottom with metal mixing bladesprojecting out of each shaft. Its measures 67 inches long by 27 ? inches wide by 20 ? inch es deep on the inside and 36 inches deep on the outside, and has threemesh guar ds on top that are interlocked with a magnetic switch which provides the operato r the ability to lift the guards up to varying heights before the shut offswitc h of the extruder would be activated. The employee was responsible for adding wa ter and flour to the dough while it was being mixed by the extruder. Theemploye e was working alongside a co-worker on the same line; however, the co-worker did not witness the accident. This same co-worker found the employeeupside down in side the extruder. The only guard that was open on the extruder was the one that her body was sticking out of and that guard was all the way upand resting in t he up position. The coroner determined that the employee died as a result of she aring and crushing trauma to her torso, from contact with theaugers.Keywords: amputation, caught in, machine guarding, torsoEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977463.015 37 F Fatality Machine feeders and offbearers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":102,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61970.015 - Employee Run Over By Vehicle And Is KilledAccident: 61970.015 -- Report ID: 0627700 -- Event Date: 05/10/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977452.015 05/12/2014 Citation Oil & Gas Corp.At 3:30 p.m. on May 10, 2014, an employee stepped out of a Chevy 2500 work truck to talk with his wife who was working. The employee walked around thevehicle t o talk with his wife when the truck began to roll forward. The employees grands on was in the truck, so he attempted to run in front of the truck to stop it. His wife ran around to the drivers side and put the truck in park. The employee slipped in front of the truck and the truck ran over him. The employee was kille d froma chest injury.Keywords: run over, struck by, truckEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 977452.015 50 M Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":103,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-03-15","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Electrocuted"]},{"preventability":["Medium"]},{"howPreventable":["Lockout/tagout"]},{"incidentLocation":["Bf Fort Myers, Inc"]},{"missingEquipment":["Protective Equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["Electrical Safety training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 61990.015 - Employee Electrocuted By An ApplianceAccident: 61990.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 03/15/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name963796.015 03/19/2014 Bf Fort Myers, Inc.At 1:50 p.m. on March 15, 2014, an employee checking the electrical wiring on an appliance, unplugged the appliance and was electrocuted.Keywords: electrical, electrocuted, lockout/tagoutEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 963796.015 42 M Fatality Electrical and electronic engineers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":104,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-22","standardCategories":[{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":["Nuvo Construction Company, Inc."]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["caught in"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["lockout/tagout"]},{"incidentLocation":["aggregate bins","guard rails","metal bar","turn head"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62071.015 - Employee Is Caught-In Moving Equipment And KilledAccident: 62071.015 -- Report ID: 0523400 -- Event Date: 05/22/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977781.015 05/22/2014 Nuvo Construction Company, Inc.At 12:30 a.m. on May 22, 2014 an employee was repairing a malfunctioning sensor for the aggregate bins that had malfunctioned earlier that evening. Theemployee was inside the guardrails at the top of the plant, repairing a sensor for the a ggregate bins and the \"turn head\" (diverting equipment) that takes theaggregate from the conveyor and distributes it to the bins. The turn head crushed the emp loyee against a metal bar that was attached to the guard rail. Theemployee was later found dead by a co-worker. He was caught between the turn head and the gua rd rail.Keywords: caught in, lockout/tagout, pinnedEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977781.015 39 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":105,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-20","standardCategories":[{"Email":[]},{"URL":[]},{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":[]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Overexposed To Crude Oil Fumes"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Entry assessment and harness with stand-by extraction equipment was not used."]},{"incidentLocation":["tank railcar"]},{"missingEquipment":["harness with stand-by extraction equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62089.015 - Employee Overexposed To Crude Oil Fumes Is KilledAccident: 62089.015 -- Report ID: 0524530 -- Event Date: 05/20/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977916.015 05/21/2014 Environmental Remediation And Recovery, Inc.At 2:00 p.m. on May 20, 2014, Employee #1 was in a tank railcar confined space c ontaining residual sweet crude oil without prior entry assessment and without wearing a harness with stand-by extraction equipment. While Employee #1 was shovel ing crude oil inside a permit-required confined space tank railcar. Employee #1was wearing a Level C suit, full face supplied air respirator (SAR), MSA Type-C Ultraview, attached to shop air and filter pot with no carbon monoxide filtratio n. Oneof Employee #1' s co-workers was acting as the entry supervisor and remai ned outside of the tank. After Employee #1 had been working inside the tank for 40minutes, he informed his co-worker that he wanted to exit at which point his co-worker lowered a ladder into the tank. Employee #1 collapsed against the ladd er.In-house employees attempted entry rescue three times before 911 was called, 65 minutes after the Employee #1 had collapsed. Fire and rescue service was abl eto extract the Employee #1 two hours after the employee collapse. An autopsy d etermined Employee #1's cause of death as cardiac arrhythmia which was causedby difluoroethane intoxication.Keywords: access/egress, collapse, confined space, emergency response, fire brigade/department, hoist, ladder, railroad, toxic atmosphereEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977916.015 27 M Fatality Laborers, except construction","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":106,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-19","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Employee Struck-By Crane Is Killed"]},{"preventability":["low","medium","high"]},{"howPreventable":["proper training, safer conditions, and/or better oversight of the worksite"]},{"incidentLocation":["Bay#1"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE or safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62109.015 - Employee Struck-By Crane Is KilledAccident: 62109.015 -- Report ID: 0521700 -- Event Date: 05/19/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977446.015 05/19/2014 Mid-West Mfg, LlcAt 3:45 a.m. on May 19, 2014, a 33-year old male, mill hand employee was attempt ing to lift a large bundle of steel tubes with an overhead crane. After completing his regularly assigned duties cutting bar stock, the employee, proceeded to B ay#1 to move a load of metal pipes, weighing approximately 6,000 lbs., from a transfer table to an adjacent staging area by using a crane. The employee was atte mpting to lift the bundle of metal pipes when something caused the bundle to swing which, in turn, struck and pinned the employee between the load and the barri er guard of a nearby machine. The employee was taken to hospital where he waspr onounced dead later that day.Keywords: crane, pinned, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977446.015 33 M Fatality Stock handlers and baggers","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":107,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-19","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Forklift"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Employee training or safety awareness programs or proper use of safety equipment"]},{"incidentLocation":["Trucker's trailer"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Safety awareness"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62129.015 - Employee Struck By Forklift Is KilledAccident: 62129.015 -- Report ID: 0636900 -- Event Date: 05/19/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977985.015 05/20/2014 Norco CorporationAt 1:15 p.m. on May 19, 2014, an independent contractor employee leased out his truck and trailer to a company for the purpose of transporting loads between customers. The contractor was discussing the cargo loading requirements with the s hipper within 5 foot of his trailer when the contractor walked backwards while arguing about the tie down requests. He stepped into the path of a moving forkli ft. The contractor was struck by a board extending out form the rear of the load , andcaught his right foot under the left rear tire of the forklift, which pull ed him to the ground. The forklift ran over the contractor's right side, crushin g his right foot andhip. The employee was killed in the accident.Keywords: powered industrial vehicle, run over, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 977985.015 67 M Fatality Truck drivers, heavy","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":108,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62130.015 - Employee Struck By Forklift Is KilledAccident: 62130.015 -- Report ID: 0636900 -- Event Date: 05/20/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978004.015 05/20/2014 Landmark FabricationAddressing the requirements to tie down the cargo with the forklift operator and the spotter At 4:00 a.m. on May 20, 2014, a truck driver/employee and spotter werewithin 2 to 3 feet of the forklift as it started and moved forward. The sp otter and truck driver walked backwards and the driver was too close to the oper atingequipment when his right leg was struck by the rear left tire. The fork li ft then pulled him to the ground and it ran over his foot/ankle and his right le g and hip. Thetire tread broke his right foot and ankle, pulled his jeans down past his hips, crushed his pelvis and cut a large hole into his right abdomen. The employee had roadrash from the forklift tire pulling him along the graveled yard. The employee died from the injuries at the hospital.Keywords: material handling, powered industrial vehicle, run over, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 978004.015 67 M Fatality Truck drivers, heavy","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":109,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-24","standardCategories":[{"Location":["hotel under construction"]},{"PersonType":["employee","operator","laborer"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["fall","profil fall from height"]},{"preventability":["high"]},{"howPreventable":["securing the working platform","retracting the forks","proper training of the operator","utilizing outriggers","utilizing fall protection"]},{"incidentLocation":["fourth level floor of a hotel"]},{"missingEquipment":["fall protection"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62149.015 - Employee Falls From Height And Is KilledAccident: 62149.015 -- Report ID: 0626000 -- Event Date: 05/24/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978063.015 05/24/2014 Angel Aaa Electric, LlcAt 7:15 a.m. on May 24, 2014, an employee was unloading wire spools while inside a non-approved working platform. The working platform was next to a windowat the 4th level floor of a hotel under construction. The working platform was sup ported and elevated by a sky track industrial truck; however, prior to lifting t heemployee, the working platform was not secured/tied to the industrial truck a nd the outriggers were not used. The industrial truck was parked on an incline, theforks were not retracted accordingly under the load, nor was fall protection utilized,. The industrial truck operator was not trained, and did not remain in theindustrial truck vehicle. The employee and wire spools were elevated using the working platform approximately 40 feet above ground. Upon completing the li ft, theoperator left the controls of the industrial truck and proceeded to the fourth level floor as the working platform had been positioned next to an open h ole window atthe exterior wall of the hotel under construction. The employee be gan to unload the wire spools from the inside of the working platform and the wo rking platformunexpectedly tilted to one side with the employee inside the work ing platform. The employee fell and was killed.Keywords: aerial lift, fall, falling object, hydraulic lift, scaffoldAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityCommercial building New project or new addition 4 40 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 978063.015 35 M Fatality Laborers, except construction FallDist: 40FallHt:40Cause: Installing equipment (HVAC and other)FatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":110,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-23","standardCategories":[{"DateTime":["2014-05-23"]},{"PersonType":["Iron /& Steel Worker"]},{"Event":["private accident"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Fall"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Provide fall protection, proper use of rigging, adequate employee training"]},{"incidentLocation":["Jobsite"]},{"missingEquipment":["Fall protection"]},{"missingPrograms":["Safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62169.015 - Employee Is Struck And Killed By Concrete PanelAccident: 62169.015 -- Report ID: 0521700 -- Event Date: 05/23/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978064.015 05/23/2014 International Erectors, Inc.At 12:30 p.m. on May 23, 2014, an employee was on the preinstalled concrete floo r planks awaiting the receipt of the next floor plank. The employee was part of aprecast concrete erection crew who began work at around 8:00 A.M. at the jobsi te. The crew had been assigned to erect the west stairway of the parking garage.The crew had received and set the first two planks of precast concrete of the f irst floor landing and were waiting for the third plank when the incident occurr ed. Theemployee was on the first floor deck providing crane signals to a crew m ember who, in turn, was on the ground acting as the hardline signal person for t he craneoperator. The planks were being lifted over the stairway walls, which d id not allow the crane operator to see the operation that was being performed by the rest ofthe erection crew. The crew rigged plank #18, the third plank inten ded for the first floor landing, and signaled the crane operator to lift it up t o the first floor deck.The crane operator stated he received the command to low er the plank, and in the process of lowering the plank he heard the employee pro viding him signalsyelling \u0000stop, stop, get up, get up.\u0000 The employee was standi ng under the load when the plank hit part of the structure causing it to slip ou t of the basket hitch. Theemployee was struck by the concrete plank and severe ly injured. The employee was killed.Keywords: construction, crane operator, struck byAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther building New project or new addition $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 3 30 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 978064.015 46 M Fatality Strctural Iron /& Steel Worker FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Pouring or installing floor decksFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":111,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-15","standardCategories":[{"Location":["All Steel Consultants, Inc."]},{"Person":["Employee"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Falls From Beam And Is Killed"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["Employee was wearing personal fall arrest system but not tied off"]},{"incidentLocation":["9:45 a.m. on May 15, 2014"]},{"missingEquipment":["Personal fall arrest system"]},{"missingPrograms":["Fall protection and steel erection safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62210.015 - Employee Falls From Beam And Is KilledAccident: 62210.015 -- Report ID: 0420600 -- Event Date: 05/15/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name977371.015 05/19/2014 All Steel Consultants, Inc.At 9:45 a.m. on May 15, 2014, an employee was connecting beams. Employee was wea ring personal fall arrest system but not tied off. Employee fell 29 feet.Employ ee was killed due to fall.Keywords: fall, fall protection, steel erectionAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther building New project or new addition $1,000,000 to $5,000,000 2 30 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 977371.015 35 M Fatality Structural metal workers FallDist:FallHt:Cause: Steel Erection Of Open Web Steel Joists-Bolting-UpFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":112,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-14","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["electrocution"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["safety equipment","employee training","safety awareness programs"]},{"incidentLocation":["Aarow Electrical Solutions Llc"]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training","safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62229.015 - Employee Is Electrocuted And Killed While Serving Water HeatAccident: 62229.015 -- Report ID: 0316100 -- Event Date: 05/14/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978145.015 05/14/2014 Aarow Electrical Solutions LlcAt 8:00 a.m. on May 14, 2014, an employee was attempting to locate and cut off p ower supply to water heater. While attempting to locate the power supply, the employee made contact with live electrical wiring. Employee was killed due to elec trocution.Keywords: electric shockAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityOther building Demolition XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 978145.015 34 M Fatality Electricians","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":113,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-22","standardCategories":[{"PhoneNumber":[]},{"Address":[]},{"Skill":[]},{"Product":[]},{"Event":[]},{"Organization":[]},{"Location":[]},{"PersonType":[]},{"Person":[]}],"extendedCategories":[{"TypeOfAccident":["Employee Is Killed In When Trench Collapses"]},{"Preventability":["High"]},{"HowPreventable":["Employee training or safety awareness programs, PPE, safety equipment"]},{"IncidentLocation":["Forming"]},{"MissingEquipment":["PPE, safety equipment"]},{"MissingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user experience?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62249.015 - Employee Is Killed In When Trench CollapsesAccident: 62249.015 -- Report ID: 0316100 -- Event Date: 05/22/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978203.015 05/27/2014 Contact Construction, Llc.At 3:00 p.m. on May 22, 2014, an employee was prepping form work. The employee w as near a shear wall that collapsed and partially buried the employee to thetop of the thighs. Employee was killed.Keywords: excavationAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityMulti-family dwelling New project or new addition XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation Construction1 978203.015 71 M Fatality Carpenters FallDist:FallHt:Cause: FormingFatCause:","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":114,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-22","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Employee Falls From Moving Vehicle Due To Collision And Is Killed"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Using proper safety equipment, such as a seatbelt or other restraining device, could have prevented this incident"]},{"incidentLocation":["Highway, road, street"]},{"missingEquipment":["seatbelt or other restraining device"]},{"missingPrograms":["employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62250.015 - Employee Falls From Moving Vehicle Due To Collision And Is KAccident: 62250.015 -- Report ID: 0627700 -- Event Date: 05/22/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978215.015 05/23/2014 Quapaw Co.At 11:00 a.m. on May 22, 2014, an employee was preparing to turn left onto the s taging area when a Peter Built semi truck and trailer was coming up from behindthe loader and attempting to pass the loader on the left side. As the semi was passing, the loader turned left into the semi. The loader bent in the right sid e fronttire of the of the semi, causing it to veer right towards the loader. A s the semi moved forward, the trailer struck the box blade on the loader causing the loader toturn to the right side of the road. When the loader was struck b y the trailer, employee fell from moving vehicle thus killing him.Keywords: construction vehicle, fall, riding on equipmentAccident DetailsEnd Use Proj Type Proj Cost Stories NonBldgHt FatalityHighway, road, street Alteration or rehabilitation 0 0 XEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature1 978215.015 22 F Fatality","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":115,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-02-01","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["run over"]},{"preventability":["low"]},{"howPreventable":["missingEquipment (e.g. PPE or safety equipment that could have prevented this incident)","missingPrograms (e.g. employee training or safety awareness programs that could have prevented this incident)"]},{"incidentLocation":["Xpress Transporters, Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["Safety equipment"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No!"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No!"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62269.015 - Employee Is Crushed By A Tractor Trailer And Is KilledAccident: 62269.015 -- Report ID: 0418800 -- Event Date: 02/01/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978355.015 05/23/2014 Xpress Transporters, Inc.At 9:00 a.m. on February 1, 2014, an employee was run over by a tractor trailer and found crushed under the step of the cab. The employee was killed.Keywords: run over, tractor trailerEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 978355.015 61 M Fatality Vehicle washers and equipment cleaners","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":116,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-29","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Caught Between A Door"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Ensuring roll-off vacuum container tank door is not closing"]},{"incidentLocation":["Freehold Cartage, Inc."]},{"missingEquipment":["PPE"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee training or safety awareness programs"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62309.015 - Employee Caught Between A Door Is KilledAccident: 62309.015 -- Report ID: 0213900 -- Event Date: 05/29/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978538.015 05/29/2014 Freehold Cartage, Inc.At 6:30 a.m. on May 29, 2012, Employee #1 was standing at the entrance to a roll -off vacuum container tank while Employee #2 removed residual wastetoothpaste. The door to the container suddenly closed, crushing and killing Employee #1.Keywords: caught in, crushingEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 978538.015 31 M Fatality Truck drivers, heavy","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":117,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[],"evaluations":[],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62310.015 - Employee Caught In Between Gear Arm Is KilledAccident: 62310.015 -- Report ID: 0524200 -- Event Date: 05/27/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978559.015 05/27/2014 Alpha Baking Co., Inc.At 9:45 a.m. on May 27, 2014, an employee was watching two members of his mainte nance crew make a repair to correct the timing on an encoder gear box on aBaker y Equipment/Winkler (BEW) loader. Once the repair was completed, the loader was restarted to verify that the timing was adjusted properly. At that time, thegu ards that were removed prior to the repair were still off the loader. The employ ee wanted to check the oil level of the encoder gear box. At the time of the incident the back and north guards of the BEW loader had yet to be replaced from t he repair of the gear box timing that had just been completed. Before the guard sfor the loader where reinstalled, the employee, in order to obtain a better vi ew, placed his head into the opening, where the guard would normally be placed, andexposed himself to a moving part (gear arm) of the loader that intermittentl y rotated every 17 seconds. While the employee's head was in position over the top ofthe gear box, the gear arm rotated and pinched his head against the frame of the machine and caused a fatal injury. According to the Postmortem Examinat ionReport from the Office of the Medical Examiner, the employee died from blun t force trauma of the head as a consequence of being struck by a gear arm.Keywords: caught in, crushing, machine guarding, struck byEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 978559.015 31 M Fatality Engineering technicians, n.e.c.","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":118,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-28","standardCategories":[],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Drowning"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Emergency Response"]},{"incidentLocation":["Parking Lot"]},{"missingEquipment":["None"]},{"missingPrograms":["None"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62311.015 - Employee Falls Into Floodwaters And DrownsAccident: 62311.015 -- Report ID: 0625700 -- Event Date: 05/28/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978558.015 05/29/2014 Pax, LlcAt 5:00 p.m. on May 28, 2014, an employee was evacuating the worksites due to fl ash flooding. The employee waded through flood waters and reached the truckin t he parking lot. Before opening the door to the truck, the employee fell into th e floodwaters and drowned.Keywords: drowning, emergency responseEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 978558.015 56 M Fatality Welders and cutters","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":119,"isAnalyzed":true},{"entityCategories":[],"date":"2014-05-30","standardCategories":[{"Person":["Employee #1"]}],"extendedCategories":[{"typeOfAccident":["Struck by"]},{"preventability":["Low"]},{"howPreventable":["Ensure workers pay attention to their surroundings and not become distracted while walking on a job site."]},{"incidentLocation":["Dirt Road at Landfill"]},{"missingEquipment":["N/A"]},{"missingPrograms":["Employee Awareness Training"]}],"evaluations":[{"question":"Was this a positive user expierence?","answer":"No"},{"question":"Did this help to solve the problem?","answer":"No"}],"file":{},"text":"Accident Report DetailAccident: 62349.015 - Employee Struck By 18 Wheeler Truck Is KilledAccident: 62349.015 -- Report ID: 0419400 -- Event Date: 05/30/2014Inspection Open Date SIC Establishment Name978798.015 05/30/2014 Waste Away Group, Inc.At 8:20 a.m. on May 30, 2014, an employee was walking along a dirt road at a lan dfill and talking on a cell phone. An 18-wheeler operated by another subcontractor struck and killed the employee.Keywords: inattention, struck by, tractor trailerEmployee DetailsEmployee # Inspection Age Sex Degree Nature Occupation1 978798.015 50 M Fatality Garbage collectors","fileName":"accident_reports.pdf","pageNumber":120,"isAnalyzed":true}]